{"question": "Which quarter had the lowest refining operating costs for Vistra Corp. after 2024-q1?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "In which year after 2020 did Cincinnati Financial Corporation have the largest net purchases of fixed maturity securities?", "answer": "2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2021", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Investing in fixed maturity securities continues to be a priority with net purchases during the year totaling $927 million.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2021-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "We continue to emphasize investing in fixed-maturity securities, with net purchases during the year totaling $788 million.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2022-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "We continue to add fixed maturity securities to our investment portfolio with net purchases totaling $1.4 billion for full year 2023.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Net purchases of fixed maturities securities totaled $1.1 billion for the quarter and $2.5 billion for the year.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the highest gross margin among Skechers U.S.A., Inc., Home Depot Inc, and JD.com in 2024-q4?", "answer": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Gross margin was 53.3%, up 20 basis points compared to the prior year, primarily due to a favorable channel mix.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "In the fourth quarter, our gross margin was approximately 32.8%, a decrease of 25 basis points from the fourth quarter last year, reflecting a change in mix as a result of the SRS acquisition, which was in line with our expectations.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "On our consolidated profit performance at the group level, gross margin increased to 15.3% in Q4 and 15.9% for the full year of 2024, up 110 bps and 114 bps, respectively.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was Iron Mountain Incorporated's EBITDA in each quarter after Q4 2024?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "During which quarter did Home Depot Inc achieve the highest operating margin between Q2 2026 and Q3 2026?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "Which company had the highest operating margin among Home Depot Inc, JD.com, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., Crocs, Inc., and Yum China in 2024-q1?", "answer": "Crocs, Inc.", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the first quarter was 13.9%, compared to 14.9% in the first quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "JD Retail non-GAAP operating profit decreased by 5%, and operating margin was down 50 bps year on year to 4.1% in Q1, in line with our [Inaudible] moving on to JD Logistics, revenues of JD Logistics increased by 15% year on year in Q1, with strong momentum for both of its internal and external revenues.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Additionally, we achieved gross margins of 52.5% and an operating margin of 13.3%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our first quarter adjusted operating margin declined 80 basis points to 27.1% compared to 27.9% for the same period last year, but was favorable to our expectations on higher gross margins and favorable revenue, leveraging our cost base.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.6%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the highest operating margin among Yum China, Home Depot Inc, and Skechers U.S.A., Inc. in 2024-q2?", "answer": "Home Depot Inc", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Restaurant margins stabilized, OP margin expanded to 9.9%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the second quarter was 15.1%, compared to 15.4% in the second quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Earnings from operations were $206.5 million, a decrease of 5.1% compared to the prior year, and operating margin for the quarter was 9.6% compared to 10.8% last year primarily due to investments in brand building and global expansion.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter did dxc technology company achieve the highest non-GAAP EPS between 2023-q2 and 2024-q1?", "answer": "2023-q4", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our non-GAAP EPS was $0.75.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our non-GAAP EPS increased to $0.95.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our non-GAAP EPS increased to $1.02, growing 21.4% year on year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Non-GAAP EPS was $0.63.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What was EPAM Systems, Inc.'s utilization in each quarter after 2024 Q1?", "answer": "77.5% in 2024 Q2, 76.4% in 2024 Q3, and 76.2% in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Utilization was 77.5%, compared to 75.1% in Q2 of last year and 76.8% in Q1 2024.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Utilization was 76.4% compared to 72.7% in Q3 of last year and 77.5% in Q2 2024.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Utilization was 76.2%, compared to 74.4% in Q4 of last year and 76.4% in Q3 2024.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Western Digital Corporation’s free cash flow, gross debt outstanding, adjusted EBITDA, and non-GAAP earnings per share guidance in 2026-Q2?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "Which quarter did EPAM Systems Inc. achieve the highest free cash flow during the period from 2022-Q3 to 2023-Q1?", "answer": "2022-Q3", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $234 million, compared to free cash flow of $185 million in the same quarter last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2022-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $161 million, compared to free cash flow of $165 million in the same quarter last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $123 million, compared to free cash flow of $79 million in the same quarter last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What were the operating margins of Home Depot Inc, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., Crocs, Inc., and JD.com in 2026-q1?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was ONEOK, Inc.'s net income per share in each quarter after 2024 Q2?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What amount did Marathon Petroleum Corporation return to shareholders via share repurchases and dividends in each quarter from 2023 Q3 through 2024 Q1?", "answer": "nearly $3.1 billion, $2.8 billion, and $2.5 billion.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "MPC returned nearly $3.1 billion via share repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "MPC returned $2.8 billion via share repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Highlighting our steadfast commitment to superior shareholder returns, MPC returned $2.5 billion via repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What was Cincinnati Financial Corporation's bond interest income growth rate in each quarter after 2023 Q2?", "answer": "19% in 2023 Q3, 19% in 2023 Q4, 21% in 2024 Q1, 18% in 2024 Q2, 21% in 2024 Q3, and 28% in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 6, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Bond interest income continued to show strong growth, up 19% for the third quarter of this year.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Bond interest income, again, grew at a good pace, up 19% for the fourth quarter of the year.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Bond interest income grew 21% for the first quarter of this year.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Bond interest income grew 18% for the second quarter of this year.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Bond interest income grew 21% for the third quarter of this year.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Bond interest income grew 28% for the fourth quarter this year.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were the operating margins of Skechers U.S.A., Inc., Yum China, Home Depot Inc, and JD.com in 2024-q2?", "answer": "9.6%, 9.9%, 15.1%, and 4.9%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Earnings from operations were $206.5 million, a decrease of 5.1% compared to the prior year, and operating margin for the quarter was 9.6% compared to 10.8% last year primarily due to investments in brand building and global expansion.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Restaurant margins stabilized, OP margin expanded to 9.9%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the second quarter was 15.1%, compared to 15.4% in the second quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "As JD Logistics continued to benefit from its increased scale and improved operating efficiency, its non-GAAP operating margin also increased by 370 bps year on year in the quarter, hitting a new record of 4.9% since its listing.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were the operating margins of Albertsons Companies, Inc., Kolmar Korea, and Guangzhou R&F Properties Co., Ltd. in 2024-q3?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "Which company had the highest operating margin in 2024-q3 among JD.com, Home Depot Inc, Yum China, and Crocs, Inc.?", "answer": "Crocs, Inc.", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Moreover, our non-GAAP operating income increased by 18% year on year, and operating margin came in at 5% in Q3, up 54 bps year on year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the third quarter was 13.5%, compared to 14.3% in the third quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our OP margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.1% and 100 basis points higher year over year or 140 basis points higher on a comparable basis.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our third-quarter adjusted operating margin was 25.4%, down 290 basis points from 28.3% in the prior year, driven by planned investments and SG&A.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Prudential Financial, Inc.’s expected effective tax rate, GAAP net income per share, and pre-tax adjusted operating income in 2026-Q4?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was EPAM Systems Inc.'s GAAP effective tax rate in each quarter after 2023 Q2?", "answer": "26.3% in 2023 Q3, 23.4% in 2023 Q4, 6% in 2024 Q1, 26.3% in 2024 Q2, 28.1% in 2024 Q3, and 24.8% in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 6, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 26.3%, which includes a one-time tax charge connected to the disposal of holdings in Russia and lower-than-expected excess tax benefits related to stock-based compensation.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 23.4% versus our Q4 guide of 24%, due to greater-than-expected excess tax benefits related to stock-based compensation, partially offset by higher state taxes and the impact of losses in certain non-US acquired subsidiaries.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 6%, which included a higher level of excess tax benefits related to stock-based compensation.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 26.3%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24.3%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 28.1%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24.1%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 24.8%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were EPAM Systems Inc.'s revenue, Non-GAAP gross margin, GAAP effective tax rate, cash flow from operations, share repurchases, utilization rate, and revenue guidance in 2024-Q3?", "answer": "$1.168 billion, 34.3%, 28.1%, $242 million, approximately 245,000 shares for $50 million at an average price of $204.32 per share, 76.4%, and a slight increase in revenue relative to Q2 2024.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 7, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "In the third quarter, EPAM generated revenue of 1.168 billion a year-over-year increase of 1.3% on a reported basis or 0.9% in constant currency terms, reflecting a positive foreign exchange impact of 40 basis points.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Non-GAAP gross margin for the quarter was 34.3% compared to 32.9% for the same quarter last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 28.1%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24.1%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Cash flow from operations for Q3 was 242 million compared to 215 million in the same quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Share repurchases in the third quarter were approximately 245,000 shares for $50 million at an average price of $204.32 per share.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Utilization was 76.4% compared to 72.7% in Q3 of last year and 77.5% in Q2 2024.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "For the remainder of 2024, we are expecting a slight increase in Q3 revenue relative to Q2, driven by greater buildouts in the quarter, substantially offset by higher vacation levels.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What was ONEOK, Inc.'s net income in each quarter after 2023 Q1?", "answer": "$468 million in 2023 Q2, $454 million in 2023 Q3, $688 million in 2023 Q4, $639 million in 2024 Q1, $780 million in 2024 Q2, $693 million in 2024 Q3, and $923 million in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 7, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "ONEOK's second-quarter 2023 net income totaled $468 million or $1.04 per share.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "ONEOK's third quarter 2023 net income totaled $454 million or $0.99 per share.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "ONEOK's fourth quarter and full year 2023 net income totaled $688 million and $2.7 billion, respectively.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "ONEOK's first quarter 2024 net income totaled $639 million or $1.09 per share, and adjusted EBITDA for the period totaled $1.44 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "ONEOK's second-quarter 2024 net income totaled $780 million or $1.33 per share, representing an earnings per share increase of 28% compared with the second quarter of 2023 and a 22% compared with the prior quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "ONEOK's third-quarter 2024 net income totaled $693 million or $1.18 per share which included $0.04 per share of transaction expenses.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Net income attributable to ONEOK totaled $923 million or $1.57 per share in the fourth quarter of 2024 and totaled $3 billion or $5.17 per share for the full year.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were the operating margins of JD.com, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., Home Depot Inc, Crocs, Inc., and Yum China in 2024-q1?", "answer": "4.1%, 13.3%, 13.9%, 27.1%, and 12.6%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "JD Retail non-GAAP operating profit decreased by 5%, and operating margin was down 50 bps year on year to 4.1% in Q1, in line with our [Inaudible] moving on to JD Logistics, revenues of JD Logistics increased by 15% year on year in Q1, with strong momentum for both of its internal and external revenues.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Additionally, we achieved gross margins of 52.5% and an operating margin of 13.3%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the first quarter was 13.9%, compared to 14.9% in the first quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our first quarter adjusted operating margin declined 80 basis points to 27.1% compared to 27.9% for the same period last year, but was favorable to our expectations on higher gross margins and favorable revenue, leveraging our cost base.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.6%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Prudential Financial, Inc.'s underlying earnings power, capital position, cash and liquid assets, share repurchase program, and adjusted earnings per share in 2026-Q1?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were NVR, Inc.’s shareholder returns, refining operating costs, senior unsecured notes issuance, and share repurchases in 2024-Q2?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "Which company had the lowest operating margin among JD.com, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., and Home Depot Inc in 2024-q2?", "answer": "JD.com", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "As JD Logistics continued to benefit from its increased scale and improved operating efficiency, its non-GAAP operating margin also increased by 370 bps year on year in the quarter, hitting a new record of 4.9% since its listing.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Earnings from operations were $206.5 million, a decrease of 5.1% compared to the prior year, and operating margin for the quarter was 9.6% compared to 10.8% last year primarily due to investments in brand building and global expansion.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the second quarter was 15.1%, compared to 15.4% in the second quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the operating income or pre-tax adjusted operating income of Markel Group Inc., Cincinnati Financial Corporation, and Prudential Financial, Inc. in 2024-q3?", "answer": "$388 million for Markel Group Inc. (year-to-date), $224 million for Cincinnati Financial Corporation (non-GAAP, third quarter), and $1.6 billion for Prudential Financial, Inc. (pre-tax, third quarter).", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Markel Group Inc.", "stock_code": "MKL", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Third, through the first nine months of 2024, we earned $388 million of operating income and our Markel Ventures operations, compared to $179 million in the first nine months of 2019.", "ect_filename": "financials-MKL-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Non-GAAP operating income of $224 million for the third quarter was down $37 million from a year ago, driven by an $86 million increase in after-tax catastrophe losses.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our pre-tax adjusted operating income was $1.6 billion or $3.48 per share on an after-tax basis for the third quarter of 2024 and $9.98 on a year-to-date basis, which is up 6%.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2024-q1 did Cincinnati Financial Corporation recognize the largest after-tax change in the fair value of equity securities still held?", "answer": "Q3 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Net income of $312 million for the second-quarter of 2024 included recognition of $112 million on an after-tax basis for the increase in fair value of equity securities still held.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Net income of $820 million for the third quarter of 2024 included recognition of $645 million on an after-tax basis for the increase in fair value of equity securities still held.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Net income was $405 million for the fourth quarter of 2024 and included recognition of $107 million on an after-tax basis for the decrease in fair value of equity securities still held, an unfavorable swing of $931 million from the same period a year ago.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "Which quarter after 2023-Q1 did ONEOK, Inc. achieve the highest adjusted EBITDA?", "answer": "Q4 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 7, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Second-quarter adjusted EBITDA totaled $971 million, a 10% increase year over year.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Third quarter adjusted EBITDA totaled more than $1 billion, an 11% increase year over year.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Adjusted EBITDA totaled more than $1.5 billion in the fourth quarter of 2023 and more than $5.2 billion for the full year.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "ONEOK's first quarter 2024 net income totaled $639 million or $1.09 per share, and adjusted EBITDA for the period totaled $1.44 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Second-quarter adjusted EBITDA totaled $1.6 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Third-quarter adjusted EBITDA totaled $1.55 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Adjusted EBITDA totaled nearly $2.2 billion in the fourth quarter of 2024 and more than $6.7 billion for the full year.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2023 did Marathon Petroleum Corporation have the lowest refining operating costs?", "answer": "Q2 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $6.14 per barrel in the first quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $4.97 per barrel in the second quarter, lower, sequentially, primarily due to higher throughputs, lower project-related expenses associated with reduced turnaround activity, and lower energy costs.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $5.30 per barrel in the third quarter, higher sequentially primarily due to lower throughputs and higher project-related expenses associated with increased turnaround activity.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our refineries ran at 94% utilization, processing nearly 2.8 million barrels of crude per day, and refining operating costs were $5.26 per barrel in the fourth quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Cincinnati Financial Corporation’s net income, net written premiums growth, and property casualty underwriting expense ratio in 2024-Q2?", "answer": "$312 million, strong and profitable growth, 14% growth with 12% growth in agency renewal premiums and 34% in new business premiums, and 0.5 percentage points higher than last year.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Net income of $312 million for the second-quarter of 2024 included recognition of $112 million on an after-tax basis for the increase in fair value of equity securities still held.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our consolidated property casualty net written premiums grew 14% for the quarter, including 12% growth in agency renewal premiums and 34% in new business premiums.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "The second quarter 2024 property casualty underwriting expense ratio was 0.5 percentage points higher than last year, reflecting higher levels of profit-sharing commissions for our agencies and employee-related expenses.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Cincinnati Financial Corporation’s net income, net written premiums growth, bond interest income growth, and property casualty underwriting expense ratio change for 2024-q2?", "answer": "$312 million, 14%, 18%, and 0.5 percentage points higher.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Net income of $312 million for the second-quarter of 2024 included recognition of $112 million on an after-tax basis for the increase in fair value of equity securities still held.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our consolidated property casualty net written premiums grew 14% for the quarter, including 12% growth in agency renewal premiums and 34% in new business premiums.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Bond interest income grew 18% for the second quarter of this year.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "The second quarter 2024 property casualty underwriting expense ratio was 0.5 percentage points higher than last year, reflecting higher levels of profit-sharing commissions for our agencies and employee-related expenses.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Marathon Petroleum Corporation’s operating costs per barrel, fourth quarter refining margins, and operating cash flow in 2026-q4?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "Which company had the highest effective tax rate among Home Depot Inc, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., and Yum China in 2024-q2?", "answer": "Yum China", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "In the second quarter, our effective tax rate was 24.5%, compared to 24.4% in the second quarter of fiscal 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our effective tax rate for the second quarter was 19.7% compared to 17.7% in the prior year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our effective tax rate was 25.2% in the second quarter, on par with the same period last year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Cincinnati Financial Corporation’s net income, operating income, premium growth, net written premiums growth, bond interest income growth, and property casualty underwriting expense ratio changes in 2024-Q2?", "answer": "$312 million, $204 million, strong and profitable, 14%, 18%, and 0.5 percentage points higher.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 6, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Net income of $312 million for the second-quarter of 2024 included recognition of $112 million on an after-tax basis for the increase in fair value of equity securities still held.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Non-GAAP operating income of $204 million for the second quarter was up $13 million from a year ago.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We had strong second-quarter premium growth and believe it is profitable growth.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our consolidated property casualty net written premiums grew 14% for the quarter, including 12% growth in agency renewal premiums and 34% in new business premiums.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Bond interest income grew 18% for the second quarter of this year.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "The second quarter 2024 property casualty underwriting expense ratio was 0.5 percentage points higher than last year, reflecting higher levels of profit-sharing commissions for our agencies and employee-related expenses.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "During which quarter in 2026 did Marathon Petroleum Corporation return the most capital via share repurchases and dividends?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "Which company had the highest operating margin among JD.com, Yum China, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., and Home Depot Inc in 2024-q2?", "answer": "Home Depot Inc", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "As JD Logistics continued to benefit from its increased scale and improved operating efficiency, its non-GAAP operating margin also increased by 370 bps year on year in the quarter, hitting a new record of 4.9% since its listing.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Restaurant margins stabilized, OP margin expanded to 9.9%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Earnings from operations were $206.5 million, a decrease of 5.1% compared to the prior year, and operating margin for the quarter was 9.6% compared to 10.8% last year primarily due to investments in brand building and global expansion.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the second quarter was 15.1%, compared to 15.4% in the second quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Aon plc’s operating margin expansion, adjusted EPS growth, and adjusted operating margin expansion in 2023-q2?", "answer": "110 basis points, 5%, and 60 basis points.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Aon plc", "stock_code": "AON", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "In Q2, we translated 6% organic revenue growth into 110 basis points of operating margin expansion, net of ongoing investment in the business for long-term growth.", "ect_filename": "financials-AON-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Aon plc", "stock_code": "AON", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We translated strong adjusted operating income growth into adjusted EPS growth of 5% in Q2 and 6% year to date.", "ect_filename": "financials-AON-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Aon plc", "stock_code": "AON", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "If we consider the combined historic margin profile of Aon and NFP, including two-thirds of NFP's results from the second quarter of 2023, adjusted operating margins expanded 60 basis points in Q2 and 80 basis points year-to-date, which is how we think about ongoing margin expansion.", "ect_filename": "financials-AON-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the highest operating margin among Home Depot Inc, Yum China, JD.com, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., and Crocs, Inc. in 2024-Q1?", "answer": "Crocs, Inc.", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the first quarter was 13.9%, compared to 14.9% in the first quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.6%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "JD Retail non-GAAP operating profit decreased by 5%, and operating margin was down 50 bps year on year to 4.1% in Q1, in line with our [Inaudible] moving on to JD Logistics, revenues of JD Logistics increased by 15% year on year in Q1, with strong momentum for both of its internal and external revenues.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Additionally, we achieved gross margins of 52.5% and an operating margin of 13.3%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our first quarter adjusted operating margin declined 80 basis points to 27.1% compared to 27.9% for the same period last year, but was favorable to our expectations on higher gross margins and favorable revenue, leveraging our cost base.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What was EPAM Systems Inc.'s GAAP effective tax rate in each quarter after 2023 Q3?", "answer": "23.4% in 2023 Q4, 6% in 2024 Q1, 26.3% in 2024 Q2, 28.1% in 2024 Q3, and 24.8% in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 23.4% versus our Q4 guide of 24%, due to greater-than-expected excess tax benefits related to stock-based compensation, partially offset by higher state taxes and the impact of losses in certain non-US acquired subsidiaries.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 6%, which included a higher level of excess tax benefits related to stock-based compensation.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 26.3%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24.3%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 28.1%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24.1%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 24.8%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was EPAM Systems Inc.'s GAAP effective tax rate in each quarter after 2024 Q1?", "answer": "26.3% in 2024 Q2, 28.1% in 2024 Q3, and 24.8% in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 26.3%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24.3%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 28.1%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24.1%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 24.8%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "During which quarter did Realty Income Corporation have the highest occupancy rate from 2023-Q1 to 2024-Q1?", "answer": "both Q1 and Q2 in 2023", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Realty Income Corporation", "stock_code": "O", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "For the first quarter, we are pleased to report occupancy of 99%, matching last quarter for the highest rate at the end of a reporting period in over 20 years.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-O-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Realty Income Corporation", "stock_code": "O", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Shifting to operations, our portfolio continues to perform, and we ended the quarter with occupancy of 99%, the third consecutive quarter at that level.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-O-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Realty Income Corporation", "stock_code": "O", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "At the end of the quarter, occupancy was 98.8%.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-O-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Realty Income Corporation", "stock_code": "O", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "At year-end, occupancy was 98.6%, a 20 basis point decline from the prior quarter as a result of expected client move-outs.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-O-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Realty Income Corporation", "stock_code": "O", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "We finished the quarter with occupancy of 98.6%, consistent with the prior quarter and our projections.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-O-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What was Western Digital Corporation's gross margin in each quarter from 2022-Q3 to 2024-Q1?", "answer": "31.7%, 32.3%, 26.7%, 17.4%, 11%, 3.9%, and 4.1%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 7, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We delivered excellent performance in the quarter, with revenue of $4.4 billion and non-GAAP gross margin of 31.7%, both of which are at the higher end of our updated guidance ranges we provided in early March.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2022-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Gross margin for the fourth quarter was 32.3%, up 60 basis points sequentially and down 60 basis points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2022-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Gross margin for the fiscal first quarter was 26.7%, down 5.6 percentage points sequentially and 7.2 percentage points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Gross margin for the fiscal second quarter was 17.4%, down 9.3 percentage points sequentially and 16.2 percentage points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We reported third-quarter revenue of $2.8 billion, non-GAAP gross margin of 11%, and a non-GAAP loss per share of $1.37.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Gross margin for the fiscal fourth quarter was 3.9%, down 6.7 percentage points sequentially and 28.4 percentage points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Gross margin for the first quarter was 4.1%, which was at the higher end of the guidance range provided in July and included $225 million in underutilization expenses and 9 million in other one-time charges.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What were the operating margins of JD.com, Yum China, Home Depot Inc, and Crocs, Inc. in 2024-q3?", "answer": "5%, 12.1%, 13.5%, and 25.4%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Moreover, our non-GAAP operating income increased by 18% year on year, and operating margin came in at 5% in Q3, up 54 bps year on year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our OP margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.1% and 100 basis points higher year over year or 140 basis points higher on a comparable basis.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the third quarter was 13.5%, compared to 14.3% in the third quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our third-quarter adjusted operating margin was 25.4%, down 290 basis points from 28.3% in the prior year, driven by planned investments and SG&A.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2023 did Skechers U.S.A., Inc. have the highest accounts receivable at quarter-end?", "answer": "Q3 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter-end were $1.16 billion, an increase of $105.7 million compared to the prior year reflecting higher wholesale sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter-end were $1.03 billion, an increase of $87 million compared to the prior year, reflecting higher wholesale sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter-end were $1.19 billion, an increase of $257.7 million compared to the prior year, reflecting higher wholesale sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter end were $990.6 million, an increase of $130.3 million compared to the prior year, reflecting higher wholesale sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Prudential's institutional retirement sales, individual retirement sales, individual life sales growth expectation, international business earnings growth expectation, and adjusted earnings per share in 2024-q4?", "answer": "$10 billion, $3.6 billion, flat to 5% growth, low to mid-single-digit growth driven by sales growth of 4% to 6%, and $3.67.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Institutional retirement sales of $10 billion in the fourth quarter contributed to $36 billion of sales for the year, up 27% from the prior year.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Individual retirement posted $3.6 billion in sales in the fourth quarter, its best quarter of sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "And in individual life, we expect sales to be flat to 5% growth.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "And lastly, in our international businesses, we expect low to mid-single-digit earnings growth driven by sales growth of 4% to 6% as we continue to diversify our product mix.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "I will note that if you exclude items specific to the fourth quarter, earnings per share would be $3.67.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the highest operating margin among Skechers U.S.A., Inc., Home Depot Inc, Yum China, Crocs, Inc., and JD.com in 2024-q1?", "answer": "Crocs, Inc.", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Additionally, we achieved gross margins of 52.5% and an operating margin of 13.3%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the first quarter was 13.9%, compared to 14.9% in the first quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.6%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our first quarter adjusted operating margin declined 80 basis points to 27.1% compared to 27.9% for the same period last year, but was favorable to our expectations on higher gross margins and favorable revenue, leveraging our cost base.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "JD Retail non-GAAP operating profit decreased by 5%, and operating margin was down 50 bps year on year to 4.1% in Q1, in line with our [Inaudible] moving on to JD Logistics, revenues of JD Logistics increased by 15% year on year in Q1, with strong momentum for both of its internal and external revenues.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter after Q4 2024 did Home Depot Inc return the largest amount to shareholders in the form of share repurchases?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "Which company had the highest free cash flow among Western Digital Corporation, EPAM Systems Inc, Autodesk Inc, and Baidu Inc in 2023-q2?", "answer": "Baidu Inc", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "operating cash flow for the second quarter was $35 million, and free cash flow was an outflow of $240 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $52 million, compared to free cash flow of $82 million in the same quarter last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We delivered record second quarter free cash flow of $246 million, up 32% year over year, reflecting strong billings growth in both Q1 and Q2.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was RMB 7.9 billion.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2023-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Marathon Petroleum Corporation's refining operating costs, operating cash flow, and projected operating costs in 2024-Q4?", "answer": "$5.26 per barrel, $1.7 billion, and $5.50 per barrel.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our refineries ran at 94% utilization, processing nearly 2.8 million barrels of crude per day, and refining operating costs were $5.26 per barrel in the fourth quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Operating cash flow, excluding changes in working capital, was $1.7 billion in the quarter, driven by both our refining and midstream businesses.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Operating costs are projected to be $5.50 per barrel.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the highest net income per share in the first quarter of 2026 among EOG Resources, Inc., Enterprise Products Partners L.P., and ONEOK, Inc.?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were Iron Mountain Incorporated's 2026 annual revenue, capital investment, AFFO per share guidance, and capital expenditures?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was Yum China's system sales growth in each quarter after Q4 2024?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were jd.com's product revenue growth, general merchandise revenue growth, and non-GAAP net income in 2026-q4?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "During the period from 2026-Q3 to 2026-Q2, in which quarter did ONEOK, Inc. achieve the largest quarter-over-quarter increase in net income?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were Epam Systems Inc's Life Sciences and Healthcare growth, Americas revenue growth, Non-GAAP SG&A percentage, GAAP effective tax rate, cash flow from operations, cash and cash equivalents, and share repurchases in 2024-Q4?", "answer": "8.6% growth, 11.4% growth, 14.4%, 24.8%, $130 million, $1.3 billion, and 53,000 shares for $13 million.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 7, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Life sciences and healthcare increased 8.6% on a year-over-year basis, reflecting 5.7% organic and 2.9% inorganic growth.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "From a geographic perspective, the Americas, our largest region, representing 60% of our Q4 revenues, increased 11.4% year over year, reflecting 2.7% organic and 8.7% inorganic growth.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Non-GAAP SG&A came in at 14.4% of revenue, compared to 14.2% in the same period last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 24.8%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Cash flow from operations for Q4 was 130 million, compared to 171 million in the same quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "We ended the quarter with approximately 1.3 billion in cash and cash equivalents, which is lower compared to the same quarter last year due to our recently completed acquisitions.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Share repurchases in the fourth quarter were approximately 53,000 shares for $13 million at an average price of $241.99 per share.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2023-q2 did EPAM Systems Inc. have the lowest GAAP effective tax rate?", "answer": "Q1 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 6, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 26.3%, which includes a one-time tax charge connected to the disposal of holdings in Russia and lower-than-expected excess tax benefits related to stock-based compensation.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 23.4% versus our Q4 guide of 24%, due to greater-than-expected excess tax benefits related to stock-based compensation, partially offset by higher state taxes and the impact of losses in certain non-US acquired subsidiaries.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 6%, which included a higher level of excess tax benefits related to stock-based compensation.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 26.3%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24.3%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 28.1%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24.1%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 24.8%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were the operating margins of Crocs, Inc., Home Depot Inc, and JD.com in 2024-q3?", "answer": "25.4%, 13.5%, and 5%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our third-quarter adjusted operating margin was 25.4%, down 290 basis points from 28.3% in the prior year, driven by planned investments and SG&A.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the third quarter was 13.5%, compared to 14.3% in the third quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Moreover, our non-GAAP operating income increased by 18% year on year, and operating margin came in at 5% in Q3, up 54 bps year on year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Yum China’s delivery sales growth, store expansion, new store openings, system sales growth, occupancy costs, and effective tax rate in 2024-q3?", "answer": "Double-digit growth, nearly 300 net new stores for Pizza Hut, 438 net new stores, 6% increase for KFC, 26.2%, and 27.3%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 6, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Delivery sales achieved double-digit growth as it has for 10 consecutive years.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Pizza Hut opened nearly 300 net new stores in the first nine months, exceeding 3,600 stores.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "In Q3, we opened 438 net new stores with over 1,200 net new stores year-to-date.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "First, let's take a closer look at our third quarter performance by brand, KFC system sales increased 6% year over year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Occupancy and other was 26.2%, 40 basis points lower year over year or 60 basis points lower on a comparable basis.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our effective tax rate was 27.3% in quarter 3, on par with the same period last year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What were the effective tax rates for Yum China, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., and Home Depot Inc in Q2 2026?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "Which company had the lowest effective tax rate among Skechers U.S.A., Inc., Home Depot Inc, and Yum China in 2024-q2?", "answer": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our effective tax rate for the second quarter was 19.7% compared to 17.7% in the prior year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "In the second quarter, our effective tax rate was 24.5%, compared to 24.4% in the second quarter of fiscal 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our effective tax rate was 25.2% in the second quarter, on par with the same period last year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the highest operating margin in 2024-q1 among JD.com, Yum China, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., and Home Depot Inc?", "answer": "Home Depot Inc", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "JD Retail non-GAAP operating profit decreased by 5%, and operating margin was down 50 bps year on year to 4.1% in Q1, in line with our [Inaudible] moving on to JD Logistics, revenues of JD Logistics increased by 15% year on year in Q1, with strong momentum for both of its internal and external revenues.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.6%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Additionally, we achieved gross margins of 52.5% and an operating margin of 13.3%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the first quarter was 13.9%, compared to 14.9% in the first quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter of 2026 did EPAM Systems Inc. have the lowest GAAP effective tax rate?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were The Macerich Company's occupancy rate, sales per square foot, same-center NOI growth, and available liquidity in 2026-Q3?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was The Macerich Company's same-center NOI growth in each quarter after 2024 Q4?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was ONEOK, Inc.'s net income for each quarter from 2023 Q2 to 2024 Q2?", "answer": "$468 million, $454 million, $688 million, $639 million, and $780 million.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "ONEOK's second-quarter 2023 net income totaled $468 million or $1.04 per share.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "ONEOK's third quarter 2023 net income totaled $454 million or $0.99 per share.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "ONEOK's fourth quarter and full year 2023 net income totaled $688 million and $2.7 billion, respectively.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "ONEOK's first quarter 2024 net income totaled $639 million or $1.09 per share, and adjusted EBITDA for the period totaled $1.44 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "ONEOK's second-quarter 2024 net income totaled $780 million or $1.33 per share, representing an earnings per share increase of 28% compared with the second quarter of 2023 and a 22% compared with the prior quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter did Prudential achieve the highest after-tax earnings per share between 2026-Q2 and 2025-Q1?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was the occupancy rate of The Macerich Company, Simon Property Group, Inc., and Realty Income Corporation in Q2 2025?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was EPAM Systems Inc.'s GAAP effective tax rate in each quarter after 2023 Q1?", "answer": "20% in 2023 Q2, 26.3% in 2023 Q3, 23.4% in 2023 Q4, 6% in 2024 Q1, 26.3% in 2024 Q2, 28.1% in 2024 Q3, and 24.8% in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 7, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 20%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 26.3%, which includes a one-time tax charge connected to the disposal of holdings in Russia and lower-than-expected excess tax benefits related to stock-based compensation.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 23.4% versus our Q4 guide of 24%, due to greater-than-expected excess tax benefits related to stock-based compensation, partially offset by higher state taxes and the impact of losses in certain non-US acquired subsidiaries.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 6%, which included a higher level of excess tax benefits related to stock-based compensation.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 26.3%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24.3%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 28.1%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24.1%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 24.8%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were the operating margins of Stryker Corporation, Volvo, WH Smith, and Treasury Wine Estates Limited in 2024-q2?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were the operating margins of Visteon Corporation, Sonoco Products Company, and Ingredion Incorporated in 2024-q4?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "In which quarter did Skechers U.S.A., Inc. see the highest year-over-year growth percentage in direct-to-consumer sales during the period from 2023 to 2024?", "answer": "Q2 2023", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Direct-to-consumer sales grew 29% year over year to $939.5 million, representing nearly 47% of total sales for the quarter.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Direct-to-consumer sales grew 24% year over year to 850.4 million, driven by increases of 33% internationally and 14% domestically.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "We continue to see strength in our direct-to-consumer segment, which increased 20% and for the first time exceeded 50% of our total sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Skechers excels where comfort and value intersect as evidenced by the strength of our global direct-to-consumer business, which grew 17% year over year to $829.9 million.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Direct-to-consumer increased 9.2%, resulting in sales of more than $1 billion for the quarter, a first for the company.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were home depot inc's new store openings, total sales growth, and organic growth expectations for 2025?", "answer": "13 new stores, approximately 2.8% total sales growth, and mid-single-digit organic growth.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "For fiscal 2025, we plan to open 13 new stores.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "For fiscal 2025, we expect total sales growth of approximately 2.8%, comparable sales growth of approximately 1%, and adjusted diluted earnings per share to decline approximately 2%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "And for the year, we expect SRS to deliver mid-single-digit organic growth.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Prudential's cost savings target achievement, consecutive annual dividend increase, pre-tax adjusted operating income, individual life sales growth strategy, and shareholder returns in 2026?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were Western Digital Corporation’s total revenue, free cash flow, and adjusted EBITDA in 2026-Q3?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were Baidu Inc.'s non-GAAP operating margin, operating profit, operating margin, and non-GAAP net margin in 2024-Q2?", "answer": "26%, positive and improved, 21%, and 27%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Even with the ongoing investment in AI, Baidu Core's non-GAAP operating margin improved by close to 2 percentage points year over year to 26%, and non-GAAP operating profit grew by 8% year over year, thanks to the operational efficiency gains we continue to implement.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "With revenue acceleration, AI Cloud business continue to deliver positive non-GAAP operating profit and improved margins.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Baidu Core's operating income was RMB 5.6 billion and Baidu Core's operating margin was 21%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Non-GAAP net income attributable to Baidu Core was RMB 7.3 billion and non-GAAP net margin for Baidu Core was 27%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Baidu Inc.'s total revenue, AI Cloud revenue growth, operating margin, and net margin in 2024-Q2?", "answer": "RMB 26.7 billion, 14%, 21%, and 20%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Baidu Core total revenue grew slightly to RMB 26.7 billion in Q2, thanks to the continuous acceleration of our AI Cloud business despite the headwinds in our online marketing business.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "AI Cloud revenue reached RMB 5.1 billion, marking a consecutive acceleration to 14% year-over-year growth, while sustaining non-GAAP operating profitability in the second quarter.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Baidu Core's operating income was RMB 5.6 billion and Baidu Core's operating margin was 21%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Net income attributable to Baidu Core was RMB 5.5 billion and net margin for Baidu Core was 20%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Prudential Financial, Inc.’s investment performance, capital position, operating income, assets under management, and individual retirement sales in 2026-Q3?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were the operating margins of Skechers U.S.A., Inc., Yum China, JD.com, Crocs, Inc., and Home Depot Inc in 2024-q1?", "answer": "13.3%, 12.6%, 4.1%, 27.1%, and 13.9%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Additionally, we achieved gross margins of 52.5% and an operating margin of 13.3%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.6%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "JD Retail non-GAAP operating profit decreased by 5%, and operating margin was down 50 bps year on year to 4.1% in Q1, in line with our [Inaudible] moving on to JD Logistics, revenues of JD Logistics increased by 15% year on year in Q1, with strong momentum for both of its internal and external revenues.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our first quarter adjusted operating margin declined 80 basis points to 27.1% compared to 27.9% for the same period last year, but was favorable to our expectations on higher gross margins and favorable revenue, leveraging our cost base.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the first quarter was 13.9%, compared to 14.9% in the first quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What were EOG Resources, Inc.’s free cash flow, increase in share repurchase authorization, and dividend payment in 2024-Q3?", "answer": "$1.5 billion, $5 billion, and $0.91 per share.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EOG Resources, Inc.", "stock_code": "EOG", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We generated $1.6 billion of adjusted net income and $1.5 billion of free cash flow and returned $1.3 billion of that free cash flow back to our shareholders through a mix of our regular dividend and opportunistic share repurchases.", "ect_filename": "energy-EOG-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EOG Resources, Inc.", "stock_code": "EOG", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "In addition to announcing third quarter results yesterday, we demonstrated confidence in our ability to generate strong free cash flow in the future, as well as our continued commitment to return a significant portion of cash to our shareholders by increasing the regular dividend 7% and boosting our share repurchase authorization by $5 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-EOG-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EOG Resources, Inc.", "stock_code": "EOG", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Finally, we paid a $0.91 per share dividend and repurchased $758 million of shares during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-EOG-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "Which quarter after 2023-q3 did Crocs, Inc. achieve the highest adjusted operating margin?", "answer": "Q2 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "We delivered top-tier profitability with adjusted gross margin up 240 basis points to 55.7% adjusted operating margin of 24.1% and adjusted earnings per share of $2.58 ahead of our guidance of $2.05 to $2.35.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "For the quarter, adjusted gross margin gained 180 basis points to 56% and adjusted operating margin was 27.1%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Adjusted gross margin improved 330 basis points from prior year to 61.4%, and adjusted operating margin was 29.3%, resulting in adjusted earnings per share of $4.01.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our third-quarter adjusted operating margin was 25.4%, down 290 basis points from 28.3% in the prior year, driven by planned investments and SG&A.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "With our adjusted operating margins of 25.6% and strong deployment of our free cash flow, we delivered adjusted diluted EPS of $13.17, 9% above the prior year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter did DXC Technology Company achieve the highest adjusted EBIT margin during the period from 2026 Q4 to 2027 Q3?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "During the period 2026-Q1 to 2026-Q3, which quarter did Prudential Financial, Inc. achieve the highest sales in Individual Retirement?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was the adjusted EBITDA of Marathon Petroleum Corporation, Enterprise Products Partners L.P., and ONEOK, Inc. in 2023-q2?", "answer": "$4.5 billion, $2.4 billion, and $971 million.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Adjusted EBITDA was $4.5 billion for the quarter and cash flow from operations excluding favorable working capital changes was over $3.1 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Enterprise Products Partners L.P.", "stock_code": "EPD", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We reported adjusted EBITDA of 2.4 billion, compared to 2.2 billion in the same quarter of last year.", "ect_filename": "energy-EPD-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Second-quarter adjusted EBITDA totaled $971 million, a 10% increase year over year.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter did EPAM Systems Inc. report the lowest GAAP effective tax rate from Q2 2025 to Q1 2026?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "In which year after 2019 did Cincinnati Financial Corporation have the highest net purchases of fixed maturity securities?", "answer": "2023", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2020", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "We continue to invest in the fixed maturity portfolio with net purchases during the year totaling $291 million.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2020-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2021", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Investing in fixed maturity securities continues to be a priority with net purchases during the year totaling $927 million.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2021-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "We continue to emphasize investing in fixed-maturity securities, with net purchases during the year totaling $788 million.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2022-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "We continue to add fixed maturity securities to our investment portfolio with net purchases totaling $1.4 billion for full year 2023.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "The equity portfolio was in a net gain position of $7.2 billion, while the fixed maturity portfolio was in a net loss position of $553 million.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was ONEOK, Inc.'s net income for each quarter from Q2 2023 to Q1 2024?", "answer": "$468 million in Q2 2023, $454 million in Q3 2023, $688 million in Q4 2023, and $639 million in Q1 2024.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "ONEOK's second-quarter 2023 net income totaled $468 million or $1.04 per share.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "ONEOK's third quarter 2023 net income totaled $454 million or $0.99 per share.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "ONEOK's fourth quarter and full year 2023 net income totaled $688 million and $2.7 billion, respectively.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "ONEOK's first quarter 2024 net income totaled $639 million or $1.09 per share, and adjusted EBITDA for the period totaled $1.44 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What were jd.com's DAU growth, electronics and home appliances revenue performance, revenue, net margin, and cash and cash equivalents in 2026-q3?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2023-q2 did jd.com report the highest year-on-year net revenue growth?", "answer": "Q4 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 6, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our net revenues grow by 2% year on year to RMB 248 billion in Q3.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our net revenues grew by 4% year on year to RMB 306 billion in Q4 and RMB 1.1 trillion for full year 2023, as we navigated a mix of macro recovery, seasonality factors, and our strategic refocus.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our net revenues grow by 7% year on year to RMB 260 billion in Q1.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our net revenue grew by 1% year on year to RMB 291 billion in Q2.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our net revenues grew by 5% year on year to RMB 260 billion in Q3, of which product revenues were up 5%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our net revenues were up 13% year on year to RMB 347 billion in Q4 and up 7% year on year to RMB 1.2 trillion for the full year of 2024, of which product revenues were up 14% and 7% year on year for the quarter and full year, respectively.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2024-q4 did Prudential have the highest level of cash and liquid assets?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was EPAM Systems, Inc.'s cash flow from operations in each quarter after 2023 Q3?", "answer": "$171 million in 2023 Q4, $130 million in 2024 Q1, $57 million in 2024 Q2, $242 million in 2024 Q3, and $130 million in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Cash flow from operations for Q4 was $171 million, compared to $186 million in the same quarter of 2022.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Cash flow from operations for Q1 was $130 million, compared to $87 million in the same quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Cash flow from operations for Q2 was $57 million, compared to $89 million in the same quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Cash flow from operations for Q3 was 242 million compared to 215 million in the same quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Cash flow from operations for Q4 was 130 million, compared to 171 million in the same quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Prudential's assets under management growth, retirement sales, and cash and liquid assets in 2024-q3?", "answer": "15% growth to $1.4 trillion, nearly $15 million, and $4.3 billion.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "PGIM's assets under management increased by 15% and to $1.4 trillion from the year ago quarter, driven by market appreciation, investment performance and net flows.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Retirement strategies generated strong sales of nearly $15 million in the third quarter across its institutional and individual lines of business.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our cash and liquid assets were $4.3 billion, which is above our minimum liquidity target of $3 billion, and we have substantial off-balance sheet resources.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What were the operating margins of Home Depot Inc, JD.com, Yum China, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., and Crocs, Inc. in 2024-q1?", "answer": "13.9%, 4.1%, 12.6%, 13.3%, and 27.1%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the first quarter was 13.9%, compared to 14.9% in the first quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "JD Retail non-GAAP operating profit decreased by 5%, and operating margin was down 50 bps year on year to 4.1% in Q1, in line with our [Inaudible] moving on to JD Logistics, revenues of JD Logistics increased by 15% year on year in Q1, with strong momentum for both of its internal and external revenues.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.6%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Additionally, we achieved gross margins of 52.5% and an operating margin of 13.3%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our first quarter adjusted operating margin declined 80 basis points to 27.1% compared to 27.9% for the same period last year, but was favorable to our expectations on higher gross margins and favorable revenue, leveraging our cost base.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Crocs, Inc.'s adjusted diluted earnings per share, adjusted operating margins, capital expenditures guidance, and free cash flow expectations in 2026?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was ONEOK, Inc.'s adjusted EBITDA in each quarter from Q2 of 2023 to Q3 of 2024?", "answer": "$971 million, more than $1 billion, more than $1.5 billion, $1.44 billion, $1.6 billion, and $1.55 billion.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 6, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Second-quarter adjusted EBITDA totaled $971 million, a 10% increase year over year.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Third quarter adjusted EBITDA totaled more than $1 billion, an 11% increase year over year.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Adjusted EBITDA totaled more than $1.5 billion in the fourth quarter of 2023 and more than $5.2 billion for the full year.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "ONEOK's first quarter 2024 net income totaled $639 million or $1.09 per share, and adjusted EBITDA for the period totaled $1.44 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Second-quarter adjusted EBITDA totaled $1.6 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Third-quarter adjusted EBITDA totaled $1.55 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Home Depot Inc's sales growth, adjusted diluted earnings per share, diluted earnings per share, average ticket growth impact, gross margin, operating margin, effective tax rate, and number of store openings in 2023-q3?", "answer": "6.6%, $3.78, $3.81, 60 basis points negative, 33.8%, 14.3%, 23.3%, and seven.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 8, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Sales for the third quarter were $40.2 billion an increase of 6.6% from the same period last year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Adjusted diluted earnings per share were $3.78 in the third quarter, compared to $3.85 in the third quarter last year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Diluted earnings per share were $3.81 in the third quarter, compared to $4.24 in the third quarter last year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Deflation from core commodity categories negatively impacted our average ticket growth by approximately 60 basis points during the third quarter, driven by deflation in lumber and copper.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "In the third quarter, our gross margin was 33.8%, a decrease of approximately 20 basis points from the third quarter last year, which was in line with our expectations.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the third quarter was 14.3%, compared to 15.8% in the third quarter of 2022.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "In the third quarter, our effective tax rate was 23.3%, down from 24.4% in the third quarter of fiscal 2022.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "During the third quarter, we opened seven new stores, bringing our total store count to 2,333.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2023-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What were the operating margins of JD.com, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., Yum China, and Crocs, Inc. in 2024-q1?", "answer": "4.1%, 13.3%, 12.6%, and 27.1%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "JD Retail non-GAAP operating profit decreased by 5%, and operating margin was down 50 bps year on year to 4.1% in Q1, in line with our [Inaudible] moving on to JD Logistics, revenues of JD Logistics increased by 15% year on year in Q1, with strong momentum for both of its internal and external revenues.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Additionally, we achieved gross margins of 52.5% and an operating margin of 13.3%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.6%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our first quarter adjusted operating margin declined 80 basis points to 27.1% compared to 27.9% for the same period last year, but was favorable to our expectations on higher gross margins and favorable revenue, leveraging our cost base.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "How much did Cincinnati Financial Corporation invest in fixed maturity securities in each year after 2019?", "answer": "$291 million in 2020, $927 million in 2021, $788 million in 2022, $1.4 billion in 2023, and $2.5 billion in 2024.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2020", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "We continue to invest in the fixed maturity portfolio with net purchases during the year totaling $291 million.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2020-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2021", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Investing in fixed maturity securities continues to be a priority with net purchases during the year totaling $927 million.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2021-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "We continue to emphasize investing in fixed-maturity securities, with net purchases during the year totaling $788 million.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2022-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "We continue to add fixed maturity securities to our investment portfolio with net purchases totaling $1.4 billion for full year 2023.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Net purchases of fixed maturities securities totaled $1.1 billion for the quarter and $2.5 billion for the year.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Home Depot Inc.'s interest expense increase, share repurchases, and sales growth in 2023-Q2?", "answer": "$49 million increase in interest expense, $2 billion in share repurchases, and 0.6% sales growth.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Interest and other expense for the second quarter increased by $49 million to $428 million due primarily to interest on our floating rate debt, as well as higher debt balances than a year ago.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "And during the quarter, we paid approximately $2.1 billion in dividends to our shareholders, and we returned approximately $2 billion to shareholders in the form of share repurchases.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Sales for the second quarter were $43.2 billion, an increase of 0.6% from the same period last year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were American Eagle Outfitters, Inc.’s sales performance, customer engagement, and operating margin in 2024-Q1?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were EPAM Systems Inc.'s Americas revenue growth, non-GAAP SG&A, non-GAAP diluted EPS, cash flow from operations, cash and cash equivalents, utilization rate, and effective tax rate in 2024-Q4?", "answer": "11.4%, 14.4%, $2.84, $130 million, $1.3 billion, 76.2%, and approximately 24% for non-GAAP effective tax rate.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 7, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "From a geographic perspective, the Americas, our largest region, representing 60% of our Q4 revenues, increased 11.4% year over year, reflecting 2.7% organic and 8.7% inorganic growth.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Non-GAAP SG&A came in at 14.4% of revenue, compared to 14.2% in the same period last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our non-GAAP diluted EPS was $2.84, reflecting an increase of $0.09 or 3.3% compared to the same quarter in 2023.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Cash flow from operations for Q4 was 130 million, compared to 171 million in the same quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "We ended the quarter with approximately 1.3 billion in cash and cash equivalents, which is lower compared to the same quarter last year due to our recently completed acquisitions.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Utilization was 76.2%, compared to 74.4% in Q4 of last year and 76.4% in Q3 2024.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We expect our GAAP effective tax rate to be approximately 26% and our non-GAAP effective tax rate to be approximately 24%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Simon Property Group, Inc.’s dividend increase, funds from operations, and occupancy costs in 2024-q2?", "answer": "8.1%, $1.09 billion or $2.90 per share, and 12.7%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Simon Property Group, Inc.", "stock_code": "SPG", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Today, we announced our dividend of $2 per share for the second quarter, a year-over-year increase of 8.1%.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-SPG-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Simon Property Group, Inc.", "stock_code": "SPG", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Second quarter funds from operations were $1.09 billion or $2.90 per share compared to $1.800 billion or $2.88 per share last year.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-SPG-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Simon Property Group, Inc.", "stock_code": "SPG", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our occupancy cost at the end of the second quarter was 12.7%.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-SPG-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "Which quarter during the period from 2023-Q4 to 2024-Q3 did ONEOK, Inc. achieve the highest adjusted EBITDA?", "answer": "2024-Q2, with an adjusted EBITDA of $1.6 billion.", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Adjusted EBITDA totaled more than $1.5 billion in the fourth quarter of 2023 and more than $5.2 billion for the full year.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "ONEOK's first quarter 2024 net income totaled $639 million or $1.09 per share, and adjusted EBITDA for the period totaled $1.44 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Second-quarter adjusted EBITDA totaled $1.6 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Third-quarter adjusted EBITDA totaled $1.55 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What were the operating margins of Crocs, Inc., Skechers U.S.A., Inc., Yum China, and Home Depot Inc in 2024-q1?", "answer": "27.1%, 13.3%, 12.6%, and 13.9%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our first quarter adjusted operating margin declined 80 basis points to 27.1% compared to 27.9% for the same period last year, but was favorable to our expectations on higher gross margins and favorable revenue, leveraging our cost base.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Additionally, we achieved gross margins of 52.5% and an operating margin of 13.3%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.6%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the first quarter was 13.9%, compared to 14.9% in the first quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "During which quarter did Cincinnati Financial Corporation report the lowest property casualty combined ratio between late 2026 and mid-2027?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "In which quarter did epam systems inc have the lowest GAAP effective tax rate in 2025?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were The Macerich Company's occupancy rate, sales per square foot, same-center NOI growth, and available liquidity in 2024-Q3?", "answer": "95.4%, $910, 1.9%, and $667 million.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "The Macerich Company", "stock_code": "MAC", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our occupancy, leasing activity, and same-store NOI improved over the previous quarter.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-MAC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "The Macerich Company", "stock_code": "MAC", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Excluding the Eddy assets, our sales per square foot was $910, our occupancy rate was 95.4%, same-store NOI was 2.8%, and traffic was up 1.6%.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-MAC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "The Macerich Company", "stock_code": "MAC", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Same-center NOI increased 1.9% during the quarter, both when excluding and including lease termination income, and was 2.8% when excluding the Eddy group of assets in our portfolio.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-MAC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "The Macerich Company", "stock_code": "MAC", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We currently have approximately $667 million of available liquidity, which takes into account both the recent PPRT acquisition closing and the Queens Center refinance.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-MAC-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What were McKesson Corporation’s market expansion focus areas, total revenue growth, and free cash flow in 2024?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "In which quarter did EPAM Systems Inc. have the highest GAAP effective tax rate between 2023-Q4 and 2024-Q3?", "answer": "2024-Q3", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 23.4% versus our Q4 guide of 24%, due to greater-than-expected excess tax benefits related to stock-based compensation, partially offset by higher state taxes and the impact of losses in certain non-US acquired subsidiaries.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 6%, which included a higher level of excess tax benefits related to stock-based compensation.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 26.3%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24.3%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 28.1%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24.1%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company among Tenaris S.A., Expeditors International of Washington, Inc., Grenke, Kalbe Farma, Mitra Adiperkasa, Linde Plc, and Ameren Corporation reported the highest quarterly sales record in 2024-Q1?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were Skechers U.S.A., Inc.'s accounts receivable amounts at the end of each quarter after 2023 Q2?", "answer": "$929.4 million in 2023 Q3, $860.3 million in 2023 Q4, $1.16 billion in 2024 Q1, $1.03 billion in 2024 Q2, $1.19 billion in 2024 Q3, and $990.6 million in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 6, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter end were 929.4 million, essentially flat compared to the prior year and in line with our wholesale business.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter end were $860.3 million, essentially flat compared to the prior year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter-end were $1.16 billion, an increase of $105.7 million compared to the prior year reflecting higher wholesale sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter-end were $1.03 billion, an increase of $87 million compared to the prior year, reflecting higher wholesale sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter-end were $1.19 billion, an increase of $257.7 million compared to the prior year, reflecting higher wholesale sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter end were $990.6 million, an increase of $130.3 million compared to the prior year, reflecting higher wholesale sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was EPAM Systems Inc.'s GAAP income from operations as a percentage of revenue in each quarter from Q4 2022 to Q3 2023?", "answer": "13.8%, 9.9%, 12.3%, and 9.9%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "GAAP income from operations was 170 million or 13.8% of revenue in the quarter, compared to 166 million or 15% of revenue in Q4 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2022-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "GAAP income from operations was $111 million or 9.5% of revenue in the quarter, compared to $120 million or 9.9% of revenue in Q1 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "GAAP income from operations was $121 million or 10.5% of revenue in the quarter, compared to $144 million or 12.3% of revenue in Q2 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "GAAP income from operations was $114 million or 9.9% of revenue in the quarter compared to $180 million or 14.7% of revenue in Q3 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the free cash flow of Autodesk Inc, DXC Technology Company, Baidu Inc, Western Digital Corporation, and EPAM Systems Inc in Q2 2023?", "answer": "Record free cash flow, $17 million, RMB 7.9 billion, outflow of $240 million, and $82 million.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Today, we reported record second quarter revenue, non-GAAP operating margin, and free cash flow.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow of $17 million, leaving us a little better than breakeven free cash flow for the first 6 months of the year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was RMB 7.9 billion.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "operating cash flow for the second quarter was $35 million, and free cash flow was an outflow of $240 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $52 million, compared to free cash flow of $82 million in the same quarter last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Skechers U.S.A., Inc.’s sales growth, store count, gross margin, effective tax rate, and cash position in Q3 2024?", "answer": "$2.35 billion sales with a 16% growth, 3,589 stores, 52.1% gross margin, 14.7% effective tax rate, and $1.6 billion in cash.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "The third quarter marked a new quarterly sales record as we achieved $2.35 billion in sales, an increase of 16% or $323 million.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "This brings our third-party store count at quarter-end to 3,589.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Gross margin was 52.1%, down 80 basis points compared to the prior year, primarily due to a lower average selling price from slightly higher levels of promotional activity in certain markets.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our effective tax rate for the third quarter was 14.7% compared to 19.5% in the prior year, reflecting the release of certain allowances and other provision adjustments.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We ended the quarter with $1.6 billion in cash, cash equivalents, and investments and maintained liquidity of $2.42 billion when including our revolving credit facility.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Marathon Petroleum Corporation’s adjusted earnings per share, refining operating costs, refining and marketing margin capture, and operating cash flow in 2024-Q2?", "answer": "$4.12, $4.97 per barrel, 94%, and $2.7 billion.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "MPC generated second-quarter adjusted earnings per share of $4.12.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $4.97 per barrel in the second quarter, lower, sequentially, primarily due to higher throughputs, lower project-related expenses associated with reduced turnaround activity, and lower energy costs.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Slide 7 provides an overview of our Refining and Marketing margin capture of 94% for the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Operating cash flow, excluding changes in working capital, was $2.7 billion in the quarter, driven by both our refining and midstream businesses.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the highest operating margin among JD.com, Crocs, Inc., and Skechers U.S.A., Inc. in 2024-q4?", "answer": "Crocs, Inc.", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "JD Logistics non-GAAP operating margin reached 3.5% for the quarter and on a full-year basis as well.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Adjusted operating margin of 20.2% was down 390 basis points compared to prior year and above our expectations.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Operating margin for the quarter was 7.5%, compared to 6.6% last year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Aon plc’s total revenue growth, adjusted operating income growth, organic revenue growth, and operating margin expansion in 2024-q3?", "answer": "26%, 28%, 7%, and 70 basis points.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Aon plc", "stock_code": "AON", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "With this organic growth and the addition of NFP, we delivered 26% total revenue growth, 28% adjusted operating income growth, and adjusted operating margin of 24.6%, an increase of 70 basis points year over year from our combined 2023 margin baseline.", "ect_filename": "financials-AON-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Aon plc", "stock_code": "AON", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "With this organic growth and the addition of NFP, we delivered 26% total revenue growth, 28% adjusted operating income growth, and adjusted operating margin of 24.6%, an increase of 70 basis points year over year from our combined 2023 margin baseline.", "ect_filename": "financials-AON-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Aon plc", "stock_code": "AON", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Second, our organic revenue growth reached 7% in the third quarter.", "ect_filename": "financials-AON-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Aon plc", "stock_code": "AON", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "And when doing so, operating margin expanded 70 basis points in the quarter.", "ect_filename": "financials-AON-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What were the operating margins of Home Depot Inc, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., Crocs, Inc., and JD.com in 2024-q1?", "answer": "13.9%, 13.3%, 27.1%, and 4.1%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the first quarter was 13.9%, compared to 14.9% in the first quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Additionally, we achieved gross margins of 52.5% and an operating margin of 13.3%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our first quarter adjusted operating margin declined 80 basis points to 27.1% compared to 27.9% for the same period last year, but was favorable to our expectations on higher gross margins and favorable revenue, leveraging our cost base.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "JD Retail non-GAAP operating profit decreased by 5%, and operating margin was down 50 bps year on year to 4.1% in Q1, in line with our [Inaudible] moving on to JD Logistics, revenues of JD Logistics increased by 15% year on year in Q1, with strong momentum for both of its internal and external revenues.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "How did Autodesk Inc.’s billings change in each quarter after 2023?", "answer": "Increased 4% to $1.2 billion in 2024 Q1, declined 8% in 2024 Q2, declined 11% in 2024 Q3, and declined 19% in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Billings increased 4% to $1.2 billion, primarily reflecting growing renewal rates and early renewals, partly offset by about one month of annual billings for most multiyear contracts.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We had a full quarter impact in the second quarter, which resulted in billings declining 8%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We had the second full quarter impact in our third fiscal quarter, which resulted in billings declining 11%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Billings declined 19% in the quarter, resulting from the transition from upfront to annual billings for multiyear contracts, as expected, that's slightly offset by some early renewals in North America.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the operating margin of Yum China, Home Depot Inc, Crocs, Inc., and JD.com in 2024-q3?", "answer": "12.1%, 13.5%, 25.4%, and 5%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our OP margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.1% and 100 basis points higher year over year or 140 basis points higher on a comparable basis.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the third quarter was 13.5%, compared to 14.3% in the third quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our third-quarter adjusted operating margin was 25.4%, down 290 basis points from 28.3% in the prior year, driven by planned investments and SG&A.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Moreover, our non-GAAP operating income increased by 18% year on year, and operating margin came in at 5% in Q3, up 54 bps year on year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "Which quarter after 2022-q1 did Pure Storage, Inc. have the lowest amount of cash, cash equivalents, and investments at the end of the quarter?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "In which quarter did Skechers U.S.A., Inc. achieve the highest year-over-year percentage increase in direct-to-consumer sales in the first half of 2026?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was the operating margin of Crocs, Inc., Home Depot Inc, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., JD.com, and Yum China in 2024-q1?", "answer": "27.1%, 13.9%, 13.3%, 4.1%, and 12.6%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our first quarter adjusted operating margin declined 80 basis points to 27.1% compared to 27.9% for the same period last year, but was favorable to our expectations on higher gross margins and favorable revenue, leveraging our cost base.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the first quarter was 13.9%, compared to 14.9% in the first quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Additionally, we achieved gross margins of 52.5% and an operating margin of 13.3%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "JD Retail non-GAAP operating profit decreased by 5%, and operating margin was down 50 bps year on year to 4.1% in Q1, in line with our [Inaudible] moving on to JD Logistics, revenues of JD Logistics increased by 15% year on year in Q1, with strong momentum for both of its internal and external revenues.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.6%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "During the period 2023-Q4 to 2024-Q2, which quarter did Prudential Financial, Inc. achieve the highest sales in Individual Retirement?", "answer": "2024-Q2", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Individual Retirement posted $2.1 billion in sales, reaching the highest level since the third quarter of 2019.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Individual Retirement posted $3.3 billion in sales, our best quarter in sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Individual retirement posted $3.5 billion in sales, its best quarter of sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the highest effective tax rate among Yum China, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., and Home Depot Inc in 2024-q2?", "answer": "Yum China", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our effective tax rate was 25.2% in the second quarter, on par with the same period last year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our effective tax rate for the second quarter was 19.7% compared to 17.7% in the prior year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "In the second quarter, our effective tax rate was 24.5%, compared to 24.4% in the second quarter of fiscal 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the adjusted EBITDA for ONEOK, Inc. in each quarter from Q3 of 2023 to Q3 of 2024?", "answer": "More than $1 billion, more than $1.5 billion, $1.44 billion, $1.6 billion, and $1.55 billion.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Third quarter adjusted EBITDA totaled more than $1 billion, an 11% increase year over year.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Adjusted EBITDA totaled more than $1.5 billion in the fourth quarter of 2023 and more than $5.2 billion for the full year.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "ONEOK's first quarter 2024 net income totaled $639 million or $1.09 per share, and adjusted EBITDA for the period totaled $1.44 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Second-quarter adjusted EBITDA totaled $1.6 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Third-quarter adjusted EBITDA totaled $1.55 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What were the operating margins of Yum China, Home Depot Inc, and Skechers U.S.A., Inc. in 2024-q1?", "answer": "12.6%, 13.9%, and 13.3%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.6%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the first quarter was 13.9%, compared to 14.9% in the first quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Additionally, we achieved gross margins of 52.5% and an operating margin of 13.3%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "During the period from 2023-Q1 to 2024-Q2, in which quarter did ONEOK, Inc. achieve the highest net income?", "answer": "2023-Q1", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 6, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "ONEOK's first quarter 2023 net income totaled 1.05 billion, or $2.34 per share, and adjusted EBITDA for the period totaled $1.72 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "ONEOK's second-quarter 2023 net income totaled $468 million or $1.04 per share.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "ONEOK's third quarter 2023 net income totaled $454 million or $0.99 per share.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "ONEOK's fourth quarter and full year 2023 net income totaled $688 million and $2.7 billion, respectively.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "ONEOK's first quarter 2024 net income totaled $639 million or $1.09 per share, and adjusted EBITDA for the period totaled $1.44 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "ONEOK's second-quarter 2024 net income totaled $780 million or $1.33 per share, representing an earnings per share increase of 28% compared with the second quarter of 2023 and a 22% compared with the prior quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Prudential Financial, Inc.'s sales figures for Individual Retirement in each quarter from Q3 2023 to Q3 2024?", "answer": "$2 billion, $2.1 billion, $3.3 billion, $3.5 billion, and $3.6 billion.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Individual retirement posted $2 billion in sales, up 40% from the prior-year quarter.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Individual Retirement posted $2.1 billion in sales, reaching the highest level since the third quarter of 2019.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Individual Retirement posted $3.3 billion in sales, our best quarter in sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Individual retirement posted $3.5 billion in sales, its best quarter of sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Individual retirement posted $3.6 billion in sales, its best quarter of sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Skechers U.S.A., Inc.’s constant currency revenue growth, overall sales growth, China sales growth, and earnings per share guidance in Q2 2024?", "answer": "8.7%, 7.2%, 3.4%, and earnings per share will be down slightly due to the timing of demand creation spending.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "On a constant-currency basis, sales were $2.19 billion, an increase of 8.7%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Sales increased 7.2% to a new second-quarter record of $2.16 billion.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "In China, sales grew 3.4% year over year on a constant-currency basis.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Earnings per share will be down slightly in the quarter due primarily to the timing of demand creation spending, which is typically highest during the second quarter as we amplify consumer awareness for our product portfolio and position our brand for a successful summer and back-to-school periods.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Autodesk Inc's billings in each quarter from Q1 of 2023 to Q2 of 2024?", "answer": "$1.1 billion, $1.2 billion, $1.4 billion, $2.1 billion, $1.2 billion, and a decline of 8% in Q2 of 2024.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 6, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Billings increased 16% to $1.1 billion, reflecting robust underlying demand.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Billings increased 17% to $1.2 billion, reflecting robust underlying demand.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Billings increased 16% to $1.4 billion, reflecting continued solid underlying demand, partly offset by foreign exchange movements and a shift in mix from multiyear upfront to annual contracts versus expectations.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Billings increased 28% to $2.1 billion, our first quarter over $2 billion, reflecting continued solid underlying demand and a tailwind from both our largest multiyear renewal cohort and the pending removal of the discount for multiyear contracts billed upfront.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Billings increased 4% to $1.2 billion, primarily reflecting growing renewal rates and early renewals, partly offset by about one month of annual billings for most multiyear contracts.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We had a full quarter impact in the second quarter, which resulted in billings declining 8%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2023-q4 did Occidental Petroleum Corp generate the highest free cash flow before working capital?", "answer": "Q3 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Occidental Petroleum Corp", "stock_code": "OXY US", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "During the first quarter, we delivered over $700 million of free cash flow before working capital, despite third-party outage impacts to portions of our oily, high-margin production in the Gulf of Mexico.", "ect_filename": "energy-OXY_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Occidental Petroleum Corp", "stock_code": "OXY US", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "This exceeds the midpoint of total company production guidance, generating $1.3 billion in free cash flow before working capital.", "ect_filename": "energy-OXY_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Occidental Petroleum Corp", "stock_code": "OXY US", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "In the third quarter, our team's commitment and delivery across each of our business units enabled us to generate $1.5 billion in free cash flow before working capital, exceeding guidance in all three segments.", "ect_filename": "energy-OXY_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Occidental Petroleum Corp", "stock_code": "OXY US", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "We generated approximately $1.4 billion of free cash flow, benefiting from higher global production volumes despite lower realized oil prices.", "ect_filename": "energy-OXY_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were RELX PLC's new store openings, total sales growth, and organic growth in 2025?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were Home Depot Inc.'s adjusted diluted earnings per share, effective tax rate, and capital expenditures in 2024-Q4?", "answer": "$3.13, 22.9%, and $1.1 billion.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Adjusted diluted earnings per share were $3.13, compared to $2.86 in the prior year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "In the fourth quarter, our effective tax rate was 22.9% and for the year was approximately 23.7%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "During the fourth quarter, we invested approximately $1.1 billion back into our business in the form of capital expenditures.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter of 2024 did jd.com achieve the highest operating margin for JD Logistics?", "answer": "Q3 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "However, JD Logistics non-GAAP operating margin increased to 0.5% in the quarter, a meaningful improvement compared to a loss margin of 3.1% a year ago.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "As JD Logistics continued to benefit from its increased scale and improved operating efficiency, its non-GAAP operating margin also increased by 370 bps year on year in the quarter, hitting a new record of 4.9% since its listing.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Moreover, our non-GAAP operating income increased by 18% year on year, and operating margin came in at 5% in Q3, up 54 bps year on year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "JD Logistics non-GAAP operating margin reached 3.5% for the quarter and on a full-year basis as well.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Marathon Petroleum Corporation’s shareholder returns, adjusted earnings per share, and operating costs in 2024-Q2?", "answer": "$40 billion, $4.12, and $4.95 per barrel.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "During his tenure, Mike delivered its transformative strategic priorities and returned a peer-leading $40 billion to shareholders.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "MPC generated second-quarter adjusted earnings per share of $4.12.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Operating costs are projected to be $4.95 per barrel in the second quarter, much lower than the first quarter, reflecting the benefit of running our system near full utilization and lower expected operating costs.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What was Western Digital Corporation's gross margin in each quarter from Q2 of 2022 to Q1 of 2024?", "answer": "33.6%, 31.7%, 32.3%, 26.7%, 17.4%, 11%, 3.9%, and 4.1%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 8, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We delivered strong results for the fiscal second quarter, with revenue of $4.8 billion and non-GAAP gross margin of 33.6%, both of which are within the guidance range we provided last quarter.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2022-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We delivered excellent performance in the quarter, with revenue of $4.4 billion and non-GAAP gross margin of 31.7%, both of which are at the higher end of our updated guidance ranges we provided in early March.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2022-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Gross margin for the fourth quarter was 32.3%, up 60 basis points sequentially and down 60 basis points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2022-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Gross margin for the fiscal first quarter was 26.7%, down 5.6 percentage points sequentially and 7.2 percentage points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Gross margin for the fiscal second quarter was 17.4%, down 9.3 percentage points sequentially and 16.2 percentage points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We reported third-quarter revenue of $2.8 billion, non-GAAP gross margin of 11%, and a non-GAAP loss per share of $1.37.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Gross margin for the fiscal fourth quarter was 3.9%, down 6.7 percentage points sequentially and 28.4 percentage points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Gross margin for the first quarter was 4.1%, which was at the higher end of the guidance range provided in July and included $225 million in underutilization expenses and 9 million in other one-time charges.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter did Prudential have the highest sales from retirement strategies during the periods 2023-q3 to 2024-q1?", "answer": "2023 Q4", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Retirement strategies generated strong sales of $6.7 billion in the third quarter across its institutional and individual lines of business.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Retirement strategies generated strong sales of $16.4 billion in the fourth quarter across its institutional and individual lines of business.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Retirement strategies generated strong sales of $14.3 billion in the first quarter across its institutional and individual lines of business.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What were the operating margins of JD.com, Crocs, Inc., and Home Depot Inc in 2024-q3?", "answer": "5%, 25.4%, and 13.5%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Moreover, our non-GAAP operating income increased by 18% year on year, and operating margin came in at 5% in Q3, up 54 bps year on year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our third-quarter adjusted operating margin was 25.4%, down 290 basis points from 28.3% in the prior year, driven by planned investments and SG&A.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the third quarter was 13.5%, compared to 14.3% in the third quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the highest operating margin in 2024-q4 among Skechers U.S.A., Inc., Crocs, Inc., and JD.com?", "answer": "Crocs, Inc.", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Operating margin for the quarter was 7.5%, compared to 6.6% last year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Adjusted operating margin of 20.2% was down 390 basis points compared to prior year and above our expectations.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "JD Logistics non-GAAP operating margin reached 3.5% for the quarter and on a full-year basis as well.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was Markel Group Inc.'s consolidated combined ratio in each year before 2025?", "answer": "In 2020, it was 98%; in 2021, it was 90%; in 2022, it was 92%; in 2023, it was 98%; and in 2024, it was 94.3%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Markel Group Inc.", "stock_code": "MKL", "sector": "financials", "year": "2020", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our consolidated combined ratio for 2020 was a 98, compared to a 194 last year.", "ect_filename": "financials-MKL-2020-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Markel Group Inc.", "stock_code": "MKL", "sector": "financials", "year": "2021", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our consolidated combined ratio for 2021 was in 90, which included $195 million or three points of losses on natural catastrophes, including Hurricane Ida, the floods in Europe, and Winter Storm Uri.", "ect_filename": "financials-MKL-2021-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Markel Group Inc.", "stock_code": "MKL", "sector": "financials", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Although our combined ratio of 92% is slightly higher than our goal at the start of the year.", "ect_filename": "financials-MKL-2022-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Markel Group Inc.", "stock_code": "MKL", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our consolidated combined ratio was 98% in 2023 versus 92% in 2022.", "ect_filename": "financials-MKL-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Markel Group Inc.", "stock_code": "MKL", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "The combined ratio was 94.3%, versus 97.8% in 2023, an improvement of 3.5 points, driven by higher prior accident year loss takedowns and our underwriting actions starting to earn through, with more benefits from these actions expected in 2025 and beyond.", "ect_filename": "financials-MKL-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2024 did Baidu Inc. have the highest net income?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were Iron Mountain Incorporated's organic revenue growth, adjusted EBITDA, net lease adjusted leverage, and AFO per share in 2024-Q1?", "answer": "Iron Mountain Incorporated's organic revenue growth in 2024-Q1 was 8%, adjusted EBITDA was $519 million, net lease adjusted leverage stood at 5.1 times, however, the evidence indicates that the anticipated AFFO per share of $1.05 is for the second quarter, not 2024-Q1. AFFO per share for 2024-Q1 was not provided in the evidence.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Iron Mountain Incorporated", "stock_code": "IRM", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "On an organic basis, revenue grew 8%.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-IRM-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Iron Mountain Incorporated", "stock_code": "IRM", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Adjusted EBITDA was $519 million, an increase of $58 million from last year.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-IRM-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Iron Mountain Incorporated", "stock_code": "IRM", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "With strong EBITDA performance, we ended the quarter with net lease adjusted leverage of 5.1 times.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-IRM-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Iron Mountain Incorporated", "stock_code": "IRM", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "For the second quarter, we expect revenue of approximately $1.5 billion, adjusted EBITDA of approximately $535 million, AFFO of approximately $310 million, and AFFO per share of approximately $1.05.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-IRM-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Skechers U.S.A., Inc.’s expected annual sales in each fiscal year after 2020?", "answer": "$5.8 billion to $5.9 billion in 2021, $7.2 billion to $7.4 billion in 2022, $7.95 billion to $8.05 billion in 2023, $8.925 billion to $8.975 billion in 2024, and $9.7 billion to $9.8 billion in 2025.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2021", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "For fiscal year 2021, we expect sales to be in the range of between $5.8 billion and $5.9 billion and net earnings per diluted share to be in the range of between $1.80 and $2.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2021-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "For fiscal 2022, we expect sales to be in the range of $7.2 billion to $7.4 billion and net earnings per diluted share to be in the range of $2.60 to $2.70.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2022-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "For the full year, we expect sales in the range of 7.95 billion to 8.05 billion and net earnings per share in the range of $3.33 to $3.43.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "For the full year 2024, we expect sales in the range of $8.925 billion to $8.975 billion, and earnings per diluted share in the range of $4.20 to $4.25, representing annual growth of 12% and 21%, respectively, at the midpoint.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "For the full year 2025, we expect sales in the range of $9.7 billion to $9.8 billion.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "Which quarter did Cincinnati Financial Corporation have the highest bond interest income growth after 2023-Q3?", "answer": "Q4 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Bond interest income, again, grew at a good pace, up 19% for the fourth quarter of the year.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Bond interest income grew 21% for the first quarter of this year.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Bond interest income grew 18% for the second quarter of this year.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Bond interest income grew 21% for the third quarter of this year.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Bond interest income grew 28% for the fourth quarter this year.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Enterprise Products Partners L.P.'s growth capital expenditure estimates in each year after 2020?", "answer": "$1.8 billion in 2021, $1.6 billion in 2022, $2.4 billion to $2.8 billion in 2023, and $3.5 billion to $3.75 billion in 2024.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Enterprise Products Partners L.P.", "stock_code": "EPD", "sector": "energy", "year": "2021", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "As to capex, our growth capital spending in 2021 was $1.8 billion with approximately $2.2 billion of major projects currently under construction.", "ect_filename": "energy-EPD-2021-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Enterprise Products Partners L.P.", "stock_code": "EPD", "sector": "energy", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We continue to expect our total 2022 growth capital expenditures to be approximately $1.6 billion and sustaining capex to be approximately $350 million.", "ect_filename": "energy-EPD-2022-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Enterprise Products Partners L.P.", "stock_code": "EPD", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We continue to expect our growth capital expenditures for 2023 will be in the range of $2.4 billion to $2.8 billion, depending on any incremental system expansions and timing.", "ect_filename": "energy-EPD-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Enterprise Products Partners L.P.", "stock_code": "EPD", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our current estimate of growth capital expenditures for 2024 is now in the range of 3.5 billion to 3.75 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-EPD-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "Which quarter after 2024-q4 did Crocs, Inc. achieve the highest adjusted operating margin?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2023-q4 did Prudential have the highest level of cash and liquid assets?", "answer": "Q4 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our cash and liquid assets were $4.2 billion within our liquidity target range of $3 billion to $5 billion, and we have substantial off-balance sheet resources.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our cash and liquid assets were $4.4 billion, within our liquidity target range of $3 billion to $5 billion, and we have substantial off-balance-sheet resources.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our cash and liquid assets were $4.3 billion, which is above our minimum liquidity target of $3 billion, and we have substantial off-balance sheet resources.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our cash and liquid assets were $4.6 billion, which is above our minimum liquidity target of $3 billion, and we have substantial off-balance sheet resources.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Yum China's delivery sales growth, store expansion, new store openings, system sales growth, operating margin, and effective tax rate in 2024-q3?", "answer": "Double-digit growth, nearly 300 net new stores year-to-date, 438 net new stores in Q3, KFC system sales increased 6%, 12.1% operating margin, and 27.3% effective tax rate.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 6, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Delivery sales achieved double-digit growth as it has for 10 consecutive years.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Pizza Hut opened nearly 300 net new stores in the first nine months, exceeding 3,600 stores.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "In Q3, we opened 438 net new stores with over 1,200 net new stores year-to-date.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "First, let's take a closer look at our third quarter performance by brand, KFC system sales increased 6% year over year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our OP margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.1% and 100 basis points higher year over year or 140 basis points higher on a comparable basis.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our effective tax rate was 27.3% in quarter 3, on par with the same period last year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Prudential’s pre-tax adjusted operating income, institutional retirement sales, individual retirement sales, and international business earnings growth expectations in 2024-Q4?", "answer": "$1.4 billion or $2.96 per share, $10 billion, $3.6 billion, low to mid-single-digit earnings growth.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our pre-tax adjusted operating income was $1.4 billion, or $2.96 per share for the fourth quarter of 2024, and $5.9 billion or $12.62 per share for the full year up 6% from 2023.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Institutional retirement sales of $10 billion in the fourth quarter contributed to $36 billion of sales for the year, up 27% from the prior year.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Individual retirement posted $3.6 billion in sales in the fourth quarter, its best quarter of sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "And lastly, in our international businesses, we expect low to mid-single-digit earnings growth driven by sales growth of 4% to 6% as we continue to diversify our product mix.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "Which quarter did Marathon Petroleum Corporation return the most capital via share repurchases and dividends after 2024?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was the operating margin of Home Depot Inc, Crocs, Inc., and Skechers U.S.A., Inc. in Q2 2026?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were Vici Properties Inc.'s COVID-19 impact, dividend increase, annual revenue, incremental rent, and margin expansion in 2026?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were Imperial Brands PLC’s operating margin improvement, cash flow, operating expenses, net income, and free cash flow in 2024-Q1?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was EPAM Systems, Inc.'s utilization in each quarter after 2026 Q1?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were Baidu Inc's total revenue growth, non-GAAP operating margin, cash and short-term investments, and free cash flow in 2026-Q4?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "In which quarter did The Macerich Company achieve the highest same-center NOI growth between late 2026 and 2026?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "How many new store openings, total sales growth, and mid-single-digit organic growth did home depot inc plan or expect in 2025?", "answer": "13 new stores, 2.8% total sales growth, and mid-single-digit organic growth.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "For fiscal 2025, we plan to open 13 new stores.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "For fiscal 2025, we expect total sales growth of approximately 2.8%, comparable sales growth of approximately 1%, and adjusted diluted earnings per share to decline approximately 2%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "And for the year, we expect SRS to deliver mid-single-digit organic growth.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were the operating margins of JD.com, Home Depot Inc, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., and Yum China in 2024-q2?", "answer": "4.9%, 15.1%, 9.6%, and 9.9%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "As JD Logistics continued to benefit from its increased scale and improved operating efficiency, its non-GAAP operating margin also increased by 370 bps year on year in the quarter, hitting a new record of 4.9% since its listing.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the second quarter was 15.1%, compared to 15.4% in the second quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Earnings from operations were $206.5 million, a decrease of 5.1% compared to the prior year, and operating margin for the quarter was 9.6% compared to 10.8% last year primarily due to investments in brand building and global expansion.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Restaurant margins stabilized, OP margin expanded to 9.9%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the highest operating margin among Crocs, Inc., Skechers U.S.A., Inc., JD.com, Yum China, and Home Depot Inc in 2024-q1?", "answer": "Crocs, Inc.", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our first quarter adjusted operating margin declined 80 basis points to 27.1% compared to 27.9% for the same period last year, but was favorable to our expectations on higher gross margins and favorable revenue, leveraging our cost base.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Additionally, we achieved gross margins of 52.5% and an operating margin of 13.3%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "JD Retail non-GAAP operating profit decreased by 5%, and operating margin was down 50 bps year on year to 4.1% in Q1, in line with our [Inaudible] moving on to JD Logistics, revenues of JD Logistics increased by 15% year on year in Q1, with strong momentum for both of its internal and external revenues.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.6%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the first quarter was 13.9%, compared to 14.9% in the first quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the gross margin for JD.com, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., and Home Depot Inc in 2024-q4?", "answer": "15.3%, 53.3%, and 32.8%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "On our consolidated profit performance at the group level, gross margin increased to 15.3% in Q4 and 15.9% for the full year of 2024, up 110 bps and 114 bps, respectively.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Gross margin was 53.3%, up 20 basis points compared to the prior year, primarily due to a favorable channel mix.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "In the fourth quarter, our gross margin was approximately 32.8%, a decrease of 25 basis points from the fourth quarter last year, reflecting a change in mix as a result of the SRS acquisition, which was in line with our expectations.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the highest operating margin among Skechers U.S.A., Inc., Yum China, JD.com, and Home Depot Inc in 2024-q1?", "answer": "Home Depot Inc, with an operating margin of 13.9%.", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Additionally, we achieved gross margins of 52.5% and an operating margin of 13.3%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.6%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "JD Retail non-GAAP operating profit decreased by 5%, and operating margin was down 50 bps year on year to 4.1% in Q1, in line with our [Inaudible] moving on to JD Logistics, revenues of JD Logistics increased by 15% year on year in Q1, with strong momentum for both of its internal and external revenues.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the first quarter was 13.9%, compared to 14.9% in the first quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the free cash flow for Baidu Inc, EPAM Systems Inc, Western Digital Corporation, and Autodesk Inc in 2023-q1?", "answer": "RMB 4.5 billion, $79 million, an outflow of $215 million, and not explicitly stated but reported as a record.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Free cash flow was RMB 4.5 billion.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $123 million, compared to free cash flow of $79 million in the same quarter last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Operating cash flow for the first quarter was $6 million and free cash flow was an outflow of $215 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Today, we reported record first-quarter revenue, non-GAAP operating margin, and free cash flow fueled by strong demand and a robust, competitive performance.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What was EPAM Systems Inc.'s GAAP gross margin in each quarter from 2023 Q4 to 2024 Q2?", "answer": "31.1%, 28.4%, and 29.3%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our GAAP gross margin for the quarter was 31.1%, compared to 32.4% in Q4 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our GAAP gross margin for the quarter was 28.4%, compared to 29.3% in Q1 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our GAAP gross margin for the quarter was 29.3%, compared to 30.9% in Q2 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the free cash flow for DXC Technology Company, Western Digital Corporation, Baidu Inc, Autodesk Inc, and EPAM Systems Inc in 2026-q2?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was the free cash flow of Western Digital Corporation, Baidu Inc, Autodesk Inc, and DXC Technology Company in Q2 2026?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was Baidu Inc.'s adjusted EBITDA in each quarter after 2022-q4?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|nonfact", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was Shin-Etsu Chemical Co., Ltd.'s amortization of intangibles in each year before 2025?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was ONEOK, Inc.'s net income per share in each quarter after 2023?", "answer": "$1.09 per share in 2024 Q1, $1.33 per share in 2024 Q2, $1.18 per share in 2024 Q3, and $1.57 per share in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "ONEOK's first quarter 2024 net income totaled $639 million or $1.09 per share, and adjusted EBITDA for the period totaled $1.44 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "ONEOK's second-quarter 2024 net income totaled $780 million or $1.33 per share, representing an earnings per share increase of 28% compared with the second quarter of 2023 and a 22% compared with the prior quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "ONEOK's third-quarter 2024 net income totaled $693 million or $1.18 per share which included $0.04 per share of transaction expenses.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Net income attributable to ONEOK totaled $923 million or $1.57 per share in the fourth quarter of 2024 and totaled $3 billion or $5.17 per share for the full year.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the highest consolidated combined ratio for Markel Group Inc. before 2025?", "answer": "2021 and 2023 with both 98", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Markel Group Inc.", "stock_code": "MKL", "sector": "financials", "year": "2020", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our consolidated combined ratio for 2020 was a 98, compared to a 194 last year.", "ect_filename": "financials-MKL-2020-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Markel Group Inc.", "stock_code": "MKL", "sector": "financials", "year": "2021", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our consolidated combined ratio for 2021 was in 90, which included $195 million or three points of losses on natural catastrophes, including Hurricane Ida, the floods in Europe, and Winter Storm Uri.", "ect_filename": "financials-MKL-2021-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Markel Group Inc.", "stock_code": "MKL", "sector": "financials", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Although our combined ratio of 92% is slightly higher than our goal at the start of the year.", "ect_filename": "financials-MKL-2022-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Markel Group Inc.", "stock_code": "MKL", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our consolidated combined ratio was 98% in 2023 versus 92% in 2022.", "ect_filename": "financials-MKL-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Markel Group Inc.", "stock_code": "MKL", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "The combined ratio was 94.3%, versus 97.8% in 2023, an improvement of 3.5 points, driven by higher prior accident year loss takedowns and our underwriting actions starting to earn through, with more benefits from these actions expected in 2025 and beyond.", "ect_filename": "financials-MKL-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Marathon Petroleum Corporation’s shareholder returns, adjusted earnings per share, and refining operating costs in Q2 2024?", "answer": "$3.2 billion, $4.12, and $4.97 per barrel.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Adjusted R&M EBITDA per barrel of $7.07 and cash from operations, excluding the impacts of working capital of $2.7 billion, both of which led refining peers, and we returned $3.2 billion to our shareholders.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "MPC generated second-quarter adjusted earnings per share of $4.12.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $4.97 per barrel in the second quarter, lower, sequentially, primarily due to higher throughputs, lower project-related expenses associated with reduced turnaround activity, and lower energy costs.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company achieved the highest EMEA sales growth among Western Digital Corporation, Prudential Financial, Inc., EPAM Systems Inc, EOG Resources, Inc., Simon Property Group, Inc., Occidental Petroleum Corp, Markel Group Inc., and Yum China in Q2 2024?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|nonfact", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "Which quarter did Prudential Financial, Inc. achieve the highest institutional retirement sales after 2023 Q1?", "answer": "Q4 2023", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 7, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our institutional retirement business has leading market capabilities which helped to produce second-quarter sales of $5.7 billion, including $3.6 billion of international reinsurance transactions as well as strong stable value sales.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our institutional retirement business has leading market capabilities, which helped to produce third-quarter sales of $4.7 billion, including $2.5 billion of pension risk transfer transactions as well as strong stable value sales.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Institutional Retirement sales of $14.3 billion in the fourth quarter were driven by strong international reinsurance sales and our best quarter for structured settlements since 2016.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Institutional retirement sales of $11 billion in the first quarter included two large U.S.\nfunded pension risk transfer transactions of nearly $9 billion, driving the strongest first quarter in market history.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Institutional retirement sales of $4 billion included U.S.-funded pension risk transfer transactions of $1.4 billion and longevity risk transfer sales of $1.2 billion.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Institutional retirement sales totaled $11 billion in the quarter.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Institutional retirement sales of $10 billion in the fourth quarter contributed to $36 billion of sales for the year, up 27% from the prior year. U.S.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company among Aon plc, JD.com, Yum China, Iron Mountain Incorporated, Enterprise Products Partners L.P., VICI Properties Inc., and Markel Group Inc. reported the highest quarterly sales record in 2025-Q1?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|nonfact", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "How much capital did Marathon Petroleum Corporation return via share repurchases and dividends in each quarter after 2022 Q4?", "answer": "$3.5 billion in 2023 Q1, $3.4 billion in 2023 Q2, $3.1 billion in 2023 Q3, $2.8 billion in 2023 Q4, $2.5 billion in 2024 Q1, $3.19 billion in 2024 Q2, $2.973 billion in 2024 Q3, and $1.592 billion in 2024 Q4", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 8, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "MPC returned over $3.5 billion via share repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "MPC returned nearly $3.4 billion via share repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "MPC returned nearly $3.1 billion via share repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "MPC returned $2.8 billion via share repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Highlighting our steadfast commitment to superior shareholder returns, MPC returned $2.5 billion via repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "MPC returned $2.9 billion through share repurchases and $290 million in dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "MPC returned $2.7 billion through share repurchases and $273 million in dividends during the quarter and in October, we repurchased $500 million of MPC shares.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "And MPC returned almost $1.3 billion through share repurchases, exclusive of excise tax payments, and $292 million in dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company reported the highest free cash flow among Autodesk Inc, EPAM Systems Inc, DXC Technology Company, and Western Digital Corporation in 2023 q2?", "answer": "Autodesk Inc", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We delivered record second quarter free cash flow of $246 million, up 32% year over year, reflecting strong billings growth in both Q1 and Q2.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $52 million, compared to free cash flow of $82 million in the same quarter last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow of $17 million, leaving us a little better than breakeven free cash flow for the first 6 months of the year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "operating cash flow for the second quarter was $35 million, and free cash flow was an outflow of $240 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "Which quarter did Iron Mountain Incorporated achieve the highest revenue after Q2 2026?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "During which quarter did EPAM Systems Inc. have the highest utilization rate between 2023 Q4 and 2024 Q2?", "answer": "Q2 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Utilization was 74.4%, compared to 73.6% in Q4 of last year and 72.7% in Q3 2023.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Utilization was 76.8%, compared to 74.9% in Q1 of last year, and 74.4% in Q4 2023.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Utilization was 77.5%, compared to 75.1% in Q2 of last year and 76.8% in Q1 2024.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the highest free cash flow among Western Digital Corporation, DXC Technology Company, Baidu Inc, and EPAM Systems Inc in 2023 q2?", "answer": "Baidu Inc", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "operating cash flow for the second quarter was $35 million, and free cash flow was an outflow of $240 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow of $17 million, leaving us a little better than breakeven free cash flow for the first 6 months of the year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was RMB 7.9 billion.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $52 million, compared to free cash flow of $82 million in the same quarter last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the growth in Skechers' direct-to-consumer sales in each of the quarters from Q4 2023 to Q3 2024?", "answer": "20%, 17%, 9.2%, and 9.6%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "We continue to see strength in our direct-to-consumer segment, which increased 20% and for the first time exceeded 50% of our total sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Skechers excels where comfort and value intersect as evidenced by the strength of our global direct-to-consumer business, which grew 17% year over year to $829.9 million.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Direct-to-consumer increased 9.2%, resulting in sales of more than $1 billion for the quarter, a first for the company.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We saw significant growth in both our segments, 21% in wholesale, 9.6% in direct-to-consumer, and balanced growth of 16% internationally and 15% domestically.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the lowest effective tax rate among Yum China, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., and Home Depot Inc in 2024 q3?", "answer": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our effective tax rate was 27.3% in quarter 3, on par with the same period last year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our effective tax rate for the third quarter was 14.7% compared to 19.5% in the prior year, reflecting the release of certain allowances and other provision adjustments.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "In the third quarter, our effective tax rate was 24.4%, compared to 23.3% in the third quarter of fiscal 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the highest effective tax rate among Home Depot Inc, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., and Yum China in 2024 q2?", "answer": "Yum China", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "In the second quarter, our effective tax rate was 24.5%, compared to 24.4% in the second quarter of fiscal 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our effective tax rate for the second quarter was 19.7% compared to 17.7% in the prior year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our effective tax rate was 25.2% in the second quarter, on par with the same period last year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2023 Q4 did EPAM Systems Inc. achieve the highest utilization rate?", "answer": "Q2 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Utilization was 76.8%, compared to 74.9% in Q1 of last year, and 74.4% in Q4 2023.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Utilization was 77.5%, compared to 75.1% in Q2 of last year and 76.8% in Q1 2024.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Utilization was 76.4% compared to 72.7% in Q3 of last year and 77.5% in Q2 2024.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Utilization was 76.2%, compared to 74.4% in Q4 of last year and 76.4% in Q3 2024.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the operating margin of Yum China, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., JD.com, and Home Depot Inc in the first quarter of 2024?", "answer": "12.6%, 13.3%, 4.1%, and 13.9%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.6%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Additionally, we achieved gross margins of 52.5% and an operating margin of 13.3%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "JD Retail non-GAAP operating profit decreased by 5%, and operating margin was down 50 bps year on year to 4.1% in Q1, in line with our [Inaudible] moving on to JD Logistics, revenues of JD Logistics increased by 15% year on year in Q1, with strong momentum for both of its internal and external revenues.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the first quarter was 13.9%, compared to 14.9% in the first quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter did Skechers U.S.A., Inc. experience the highest year-over-year growth in direct-to-consumer sales during the period from 2023 to the first quarter of 2024?", "answer": "Q2 2023", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Direct-to-consumer sales increased 24% year over year to $707.4 million, driven by 25% growth domestically and 24% growth internationally.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Direct-to-consumer sales grew 29% year over year to $939.5 million, representing nearly 47% of total sales for the quarter.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Direct-to-consumer sales grew 24% year over year to 850.4 million, driven by increases of 33% internationally and 14% domestically.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "We continue to see strength in our direct-to-consumer segment, which increased 20% and for the first time exceeded 50% of our total sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Skechers excels where comfort and value intersect as evidenced by the strength of our global direct-to-consumer business, which grew 17% year over year to $829.9 million.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What was Western Digital Corporation's gross margin in each quarter from 2022 Q3 to 2024 Q2?", "answer": "31.7%, 32.3%, 26.7%, 17.4%, 10.6%, 3.9%, 4.1%, and 15.5%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 8, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Gross margin for the third quarter was 31.7%, down 190 basis points sequentially and up 400 basis points year over year, including approximately $59 million in COVID-related expenses.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2022-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Gross margin for the fourth quarter was 32.3%, up 60 basis points sequentially and down 60 basis points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2022-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Gross margin for the fiscal first quarter was 26.7%, down 5.6 percentage points sequentially and 7.2 percentage points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Gross margin for the fiscal second quarter was 17.4%, down 9.3 percentage points sequentially and 16.2 percentage points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Gross margin for the fiscal third quarter was 10.6%, down 6.8 percentage points sequentially and 21.1 percentage points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Gross margin for the fiscal fourth quarter was 3.9%, down 6.7 percentage points sequentially and 28.4 percentage points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Gross margin for the first quarter was 4.1%, which was at the higher end of the guidance range provided in July and included $225 million in underutilization expenses and 9 million in other one-time charges.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Gross margin was 15.5%, above the guidance range provided in October and improving 11.4 percentage points sequentially while declining 1.9 percentage points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What was EPAM Systems Inc.'s GAAP income from operations in each quarter after 2023?", "answer": "$111 million in 2024 Q1, $121 million in 2024 Q2, 177 million in 2024 Q3, and $137 million in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "GAAP income from operations was $111 million or 9.5% of revenue in the quarter, compared to $120 million or 9.9% of revenue in Q1 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "GAAP income from operations was $121 million or 10.5% of revenue in the quarter, compared to $144 million or 12.3% of revenue in Q2 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "GAAP income from operations was 177 million or 15.2% of revenue in the quarter compared to 114 million or 9.9% of revenue in Q3 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "GAAP income from operations was 137 million or 10.9% of revenue in the quarter, compared to 122 million or 10.6% of revenue in Q4 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter did Marathon Petroleum Corporation return the highest amount via share repurchases and dividends after 2023-Q1?", "answer": "Q2 2023", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 7, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "MPC returned nearly $3.4 billion via share repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "MPC returned nearly $3.1 billion via share repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "MPC returned $2.8 billion via share repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Highlighting our steadfast commitment to superior shareholder returns, MPC returned $2.5 billion via repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "MPC returned $2.9 billion through share repurchases and $290 million in dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "MPC returned $2.7 billion through share repurchases and $273 million in dividends during the quarter and in October, we repurchased $500 million of MPC shares.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "And MPC returned almost $1.3 billion through share repurchases, exclusive of excise tax payments, and $292 million in dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Prudential Financial, Inc.'s baseline earnings per share, capital deployment by PGIM’s private businesses, and underlying earnings power changes in Q2 2025?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2023 did Autodesk Inc achieve the highest increase in total deferred revenue?", "answer": "Q1 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Total deferred revenue increased 20% to $4.5 billion.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Total deferred revenue increased 14% to 4.2 billion.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Total deferred revenue increased 6% to $4 billion.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Total deferred revenue decreased 7% to $4.3 billion and expected result of the transition from upfront to annual billings for multiyear contracts.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Prudential's cash and liquid assets in each quarter after 2023?", "answer": "$4.2 billion in 2024 Q1, $4.4 billion in 2024 Q2, $4.3 billion in 2024 Q3, and $4.6 billion in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our cash and liquid assets were $4.2 billion within our liquidity target range of $3 billion to $5 billion, and we have substantial off-balance sheet resources.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our cash and liquid assets were $4.4 billion, within our liquidity target range of $3 billion to $5 billion, and we have substantial off-balance-sheet resources.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our cash and liquid assets were $4.3 billion, which is above our minimum liquidity target of $3 billion, and we have substantial off-balance sheet resources.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our cash and liquid assets were $4.6 billion, which is above our minimum liquidity target of $3 billion, and we have substantial off-balance sheet resources.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Skechers U.S.A., Inc.'s direct-to-consumer sales growth, China sales growth, and effective tax rate Q2 2024?", "answer": "9.2%, 3.4%, and 19.7%", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Direct-to-consumer increased 9.2%, resulting in sales of more than $1 billion for the quarter, a first for the company.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "In China, sales grew 3.4% year over year on a constant-currency basis.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our effective tax rate for the second quarter was 19.7% compared to 17.7% in the prior year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the highest gross margin in 2024 q4 among Home Depot Inc, JD.com, and Skechers U.S.A., Inc.?", "answer": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "In the fourth quarter, our gross margin was approximately 32.8%, a decrease of 25 basis points from the fourth quarter last year, reflecting a change in mix as a result of the SRS acquisition, which was in line with our expectations.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "On our consolidated profit performance at the group level, gross margin increased to 15.3% in Q4 and 15.9% for the full year of 2024, up 110 bps and 114 bps, respectively.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Gross margin was 53.3%, up 20 basis points compared to the prior year, primarily due to a favorable channel mix.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2025-Q1 did Autodesk Inc. experience the largest decline in billings?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were the operating margins for Skechers U.S.A., Inc., Yum China, Home Depot Inc, and JD.com in 2024 q2?", "answer": "9.6%, 9.9%, 15.1%, and 3.9%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Earnings from operations were $206.5 million, a decrease of 5.1% compared to the prior year, and operating margin for the quarter was 9.6% compared to 10.8% last year primarily due to investments in brand building and global expansion.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Restaurant margins stabilized, OP margin expanded to 9.9%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the second quarter was 15.1%, compared to 15.4% in the second quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "JD Retail's operating profit increased by 24% year on year to RMB 10 billion with operating margin recording a 72-bps expansion to 3.9%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What was DXC Technology Company's organic revenue growth guidance in each quarter after Q2 2025?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were Prudential Financial, Inc.'s Individual Retirement sales after 2023 Q2?", "answer": "$2 billion in 2023 Q3, $2.1 billion in 2023 Q4, $3.3 billion in 2024 Q1, $3.5 billion in 2024 Q2, $3.6 billion in 2024 Q3, and $3.6 billion in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 6, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Individual retirement posted $2 billion in sales, up 40% from the prior-year quarter.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Individual Retirement posted $2.1 billion in sales, reaching the highest level since the third quarter of 2019.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Individual Retirement posted $3.3 billion in sales, our best quarter in sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Individual retirement posted $3.5 billion in sales, its best quarter of sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Individual retirement posted $3.6 billion in sales, its best quarter of sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Individual retirement posted $3.6 billion in sales in the fourth quarter, its best quarter of sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was Marathon Petroleum's total shareholder return (dividends + buybacks) from Q3 2023 to Q1 2024?", "answer": "$3.1 billion in 2023 Q3, $2.8 billion in 2023 Q4, and $2.5 billion in 2024 Q1.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "MPC returned nearly $3.1 billion via share repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "MPC returned $2.8 billion via share repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Highlighting our steadfast commitment to superior shareholder returns, MPC returned $2.5 billion via repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter did Marathon Petroleum Corporation have the lowest refining operating costs after 2023 Q1?", "answer": "2024-Q1", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 7, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $5.15 per barrel in the second quarter, lower sequentially and due to higher throughput and lower energy costs.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $5.14 per barrel in the third quarter, flat sequentially.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $5.67 per barrel in the fourth quarter, higher sequentially due to higher energy costs, particularly on the West Coast, as well as higher project-related expenses associated with planned turnaround activity.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $6.14 per barrel in the first quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $4.97 per barrel in the second quarter, lower, sequentially, primarily due to higher throughputs, lower project-related expenses associated with reduced turnaround activity, and lower energy costs.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $5.30 per barrel in the third quarter, higher sequentially primarily due to lower throughputs and higher project-related expenses associated with increased turnaround activity.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our refineries ran at 94% utilization, processing nearly 2.8 million barrels of crude per day, and refining operating costs were $5.26 per barrel in the fourth quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was EPAM Systems Inc.'s utilization in each quarter after 2023?", "answer": "76.8% in 2024 Q1, 77.5% in 2024 Q2, 76.4% in 2024 Q3, and 76.2% in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Utilization was 76.8%, compared to 74.9% in Q1 of last year, and 74.4% in Q4 2023.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Utilization was 77.5%, compared to 75.1% in Q2 of last year and 76.8% in Q1 2024.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Utilization was 76.4% compared to 72.7% in Q3 of last year and 77.5% in Q2 2024.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Utilization was 76.2%, compared to 74.4% in Q4 of last year and 76.4% in Q3 2024.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was DXC Technology Company's gross margin in each quarter after 2023?", "answer": "21.1% in 2024 Q1, 23.4% in 2024 Q2, 22.4% in 2024 Q3, and 23.6% in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our first quarter gross margin of 21.1% was up 10 basis points year over year but below our expectation due to the revenue shortfall.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our second quarter gross margin of 23.4% was up 120 basis points year over year and 230 basis points sequentially, benefiting from our cost reduction initiatives.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our third quarter gross margin of 22.4% was up 70 basis points year over year, benefiting from our ongoing labor and nonlabor cost reductions.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Gross margin equaled 23.6%, flat year to year as we continued to drive workforce optimization and reduce our real estate footprint in the face of declining revenue.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the highest operating margin among Skechers U.S.A., Inc., JD.com, Crocs, Inc., and Home Depot Inc in the first quarter of 2024?", "answer": "Crocs, Inc.", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Additionally, we achieved gross margins of 52.5% and an operating margin of 13.3%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "JD Retail non-GAAP operating profit decreased by 5%, and operating margin was down 50 bps year on year to 4.1% in Q1, in line with our [Inaudible] moving on to JD Logistics, revenues of JD Logistics increased by 15% year on year in Q1, with strong momentum for both of its internal and external revenues.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our first quarter adjusted operating margin declined 80 basis points to 27.1% compared to 27.9% for the same period last year, but was favorable to our expectations on higher gross margins and favorable revenue, leveraging our cost base.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the first quarter was 13.9%, compared to 14.9% in the first quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company reported the highest total sales growth among Western Digital Corporation, Iron Mountain Incorporated, ONEOK, Inc., Prudential, Cincinnati Financial Corporation, EPAM Systems Inc, Enterprise Products Partners L.P., and The Macerich Company in 2024-q1?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|nonfact", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was the free cash flow of Western Digital Corporation, DXC Technology Company, Baidu Inc, Autodesk Inc, and EPAM Systems Inc in the second quarter of 2023?", "answer": "$240 million, $17 million, RMB 7.9 billion, $246 million, and $52 million.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "operating cash flow for the second quarter was $35 million, and free cash flow was an outflow of $240 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow of $17 million, leaving us a little better than breakeven free cash flow for the first 6 months of the year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was RMB 7.9 billion.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We delivered record second quarter free cash flow of $246 million, up 32% year over year, reflecting strong billings growth in both Q1 and Q2.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $52 million, compared to free cash flow of $82 million in the same quarter last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What was EPAM Systems Inc.'s non-GAAP income from operations after 2023 Q3?", "answer": "$200 million in 2023 Q4, $174 million in 2024 Q1, $175 million in 2024 Q2, $223 million in 2024 Q3, and 208 million in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Non-GAAP income from operations was $200 million or 17.3% of revenue in the quarter, compared to $220 million or 17.8% of revenue in Q4 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Non-GAAP income from operations was $174 million or 14.9% of revenue in the quarter, compared to $178 million or 14.7% of revenue in Q1 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Non-GAAP income from operations was $175 million or 15.2% of revenue in the quarter, compared to $191 million or 16.3% of revenue in Q2 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Non-GAAP income from operations was 223 million or 19.1% of revenue in the quarter compared to 196 million or 17% of revenue in Q3 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Non-GAAP income from operations was 208 million or 16.7% of revenue in the quarter, compared to 200 million or 17.3% of revenue in Q4 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Home Depot Inc.’s total sales, operating margin, and store openings in the first quarter of 2024?", "answer": "$36.4 billion, 13.9%, and 2 new stores.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "In the first quarter, total sales were $36.4 billion, a decrease of approximately 2.3% from last year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the first quarter was 13.9%, compared to 14.9% in the first quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "During the first quarter, we opened two new stores, bringing our total store count to 2,337.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the highest book-to-bill ratio among EPAM Systems Inc, Autodesk Inc, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., Marathon Petroleum Corporation, Simon Property Group, Inc., Occidental Petroleum Corp, and Prudential Financial, Inc. in the second quarter of 2025?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were the operating margins of Yum China, Home Depot Inc, and Skechers U.S.A., Inc. in 2024 Q2?", "answer": "9.9%, 15.1%, and 9.6%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Restaurant margins stabilized, OP margin expanded to 9.9%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the second quarter was 15.1%, compared to 15.4% in the second quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Earnings from operations were $206.5 million, a decrease of 5.1% compared to the prior year, and operating margin for the quarter was 9.6% compared to 10.8% last year primarily due to investments in brand building and global expansion.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter did Cincinnati Financial Corporation experience the highest growth rate in bond interest income during the period from 2023-Q4 to 2024-Q2?", "answer": "2024 Q1", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Bond interest income, again, grew at a good pace, up 19% for the fourth quarter of the year.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Bond interest income grew 21% for the first quarter of this year.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Bond interest income grew 18% for the second quarter of this year.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "Which quarter did Hansol Chemical have the highest bond interest income growth after 2023 Q3?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were Skechers U.S.A., Inc.’s sales, effective tax rate, accounts receivable, liquidity, and company-owned stores openings in Q3 2024?", "answer": "$2.35 billion, 14.7%, $1.19 billion, $2.42 billion, and 68 stores.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "The third quarter marked a new quarterly sales record as we achieved $2.35 billion in sales, an increase of 16% or $323 million.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our effective tax rate for the third quarter was 14.7% compared to 19.5% in the prior year, reflecting the release of certain allowances and other provision adjustments.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter-end were $1.19 billion, an increase of $257.7 million compared to the prior year, reflecting higher wholesale sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We ended the quarter with $1.6 billion in cash, cash equivalents, and investments and maintained liquidity of $2.42 billion when including our revolving credit facility.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We opened 68 company-owned stores in the quarter, including 20 in China, 17 in the United States, eight in Mexico, five in Korea, and three in Colombia.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the free cash flow for Autodesk Inc, Baidu Inc, DXC Technology Company, EPAM Systems Inc, and Western Digital Corporation in 2023 q2?", "answer": "$246 million, RMB 7.9 billion, $17 million, $52 million, and $240 million.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We delivered record second quarter free cash flow of $246 million, up 32% year over year, reflecting strong billings growth in both Q1 and Q2.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was RMB 7.9 billion.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow of $17 million, leaving us a little better than breakeven free cash flow for the first 6 months of the year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $52 million, compared to free cash flow of $82 million in the same quarter last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "operating cash flow for the second quarter was $35 million, and free cash flow was an outflow of $240 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Autodesk Inc.'s billings in each quarter from 2023-Q1 to 2024-Q1?", "answer": "$1.1 billion, $1.2 billion, $1.4 billion, $2.1 billion, and $1.2 billion.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Billings increased 16% to $1.1 billion, reflecting robust underlying demand.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Billings increased 17% to $1.2 billion, reflecting robust underlying demand.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Billings increased 16% to $1.4 billion, reflecting continued solid underlying demand, partly offset by foreign exchange movements and a shift in mix from multiyear upfront to annual contracts versus expectations.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Billings increased 28% to $2.1 billion, our first quarter over $2 billion, reflecting continued solid underlying demand and a tailwind from both our largest multiyear renewal cohort and the pending removal of the discount for multiyear contracts billed upfront.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Billings increased 4% to $1.2 billion, primarily reflecting growing renewal rates and early renewals, partly offset by about one month of annual billings for most multiyear contracts.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Marathon Petroleum Corporation's operating costs per barrel in each quarter after 2023 Q3?", "answer": "$5.85 per barrel in 2024 Q1, $4.95 per barrel in 2024 Q2, $5.35 per barrel in 2024 Q3, and $5.50 per barrel in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Operating costs in the first quarter are expected to be $5.85 per barrel, higher sequentially due mainly to lower throughput volumes associated with the significant planned turnaround activity.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Operating costs are projected to be $4.95 per barrel in the second quarter, much lower than the first quarter, reflecting the benefit of running our system near full utilization and lower expected operating costs.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Operating costs are projected to be $5.35 per barrel in the third quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Operating costs are projected to be $5.50 per barrel.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "For the quarter, operating costs are projected to be $5.70 per the barrel.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Marathon Petroleum Corporation's refining operating costs per barrel in each quarter from 2023-Q3 to 2024-Q3?", "answer": "$5.14 in 2023-Q3, $5.67 in 2023-Q4, $6.14 in 2024-Q1, $4.97 in 2024-Q2, and $5.30 in 2024-Q3.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $5.14 per barrel in the third quarter, flat sequentially.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $5.67 per barrel in the fourth quarter, higher sequentially due to higher energy costs, particularly on the West Coast, as well as higher project-related expenses associated with planned turnaround activity.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $6.14 per barrel in the first quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $4.97 per barrel in the second quarter, lower, sequentially, primarily due to higher throughputs, lower project-related expenses associated with reduced turnaround activity, and lower energy costs.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $5.30 per barrel in the third quarter, higher sequentially primarily due to lower throughputs and higher project-related expenses associated with increased turnaround activity.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2024-Q1 did Autodesk Inc. experience the largest decline in billings?", "answer": "Q4 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We had a full quarter impact in the second quarter, which resulted in billings declining 8%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We had the second full quarter impact in our third fiscal quarter, which resulted in billings declining 11%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Billings declined 19% in the quarter, resulting from the transition from upfront to annual billings for multiyear contracts, as expected, that's slightly offset by some early renewals in North America.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the free cash flow for Western Digital Corporation, Baidu Inc, DXC Technology Company, Autodesk Inc, and EPAM Systems Inc in 2023-q2?", "answer": "An outflow of $240 million, RMB 7.9 billion, $17 million, not specified, and $52 million.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "operating cash flow for the second quarter was $35 million, and free cash flow was an outflow of $240 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was RMB 7.9 billion.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow of $17 million, leaving us a little better than breakeven free cash flow for the first 6 months of the year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Today, we reported record second quarter revenue, non-GAAP operating margin, and free cash flow.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $52 million, compared to free cash flow of $82 million in the same quarter last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the free cash flow for Baidu Inc, Western Digital Corporation, EPAM Systems Inc, DXC Technology Company, and Autodesk Inc in Q2 2023?", "answer": "RMB 7.9 billion, an outflow of $240 million, $52 million, $17 million, and record free cash flow.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was RMB 7.9 billion.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "operating cash flow for the second quarter was $35 million, and free cash flow was an outflow of $240 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $52 million, compared to free cash flow of $82 million in the same quarter last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow of $17 million, leaving us a little better than breakeven free cash flow for the first 6 months of the year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Today, we reported record second quarter revenue, non-GAAP operating margin, and free cash flow.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter of 2026 did Baidu Inc have the highest free cash flow excluding iQIYI?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were Skechers U.S.A., Inc.'s accounts receivable at quarter-end in each quarter after 2024 Q1?", "answer": "$1.03 billion in 2024 Q2, $1.19 billion in 2024 Q3, and $990.6 million in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter-end were $1.03 billion, an increase of $87 million compared to the prior year, reflecting higher wholesale sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter-end were $1.19 billion, an increase of $257.7 million compared to the prior year, reflecting higher wholesale sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter end were $990.6 million, an increase of $130.3 million compared to the prior year, reflecting higher wholesale sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was ONEOK, Inc.'s net income for each quarter from 2022 Q4 through 2024 Q2?", "answer": "$485 million in 2022 Q4, $1.05 billion in 2023 Q1, $468 million in 2023 Q2, $454 million in 2023 Q3, $688 million in 2023 Q4, $639 million in 2024 Q1, and $780 million in 2024 Q2.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 7, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "ONEOK's fourth quarter and full year 2022 net income totaled $485 million and $1.72 billion, respectively, representing increases of 28% for the fourth quarter and 15% for the full year compared with the same period in 2021.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2022-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "ONEOK's first quarter 2023 net income totaled 1.05 billion, or $2.34 per share, and adjusted EBITDA for the period totaled $1.72 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "ONEOK's second-quarter 2023 net income totaled $468 million or $1.04 per share.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "ONEOK's third quarter 2023 net income totaled $454 million or $0.99 per share.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "ONEOK's fourth quarter and full year 2023 net income totaled $688 million and $2.7 billion, respectively.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "ONEOK's first quarter 2024 net income totaled $639 million or $1.09 per share, and adjusted EBITDA for the period totaled $1.44 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "ONEOK's second-quarter 2024 net income totaled $780 million or $1.33 per share, representing an earnings per share increase of 28% compared with the second quarter of 2023 and a 22% compared with the prior quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter did ONEOK, Inc. achieve the highest adjusted EBITDA across 2023-q4, 2024-q1, and 2024-q2?", "answer": "2024 Q2", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Adjusted EBITDA totaled more than $1.5 billion in the fourth quarter of 2023 and more than $5.2 billion for the full year.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "ONEOK's first quarter 2024 net income totaled $639 million or $1.09 per share, and adjusted EBITDA for the period totaled $1.44 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Second-quarter adjusted EBITDA totaled $1.6 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "Which quarter did DXC Technology Company have the highest free cash flow after 2023-Q4?", "answer": "Q3 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Free cash flow for the quarter was negative $75 million, ahead of our expectations due to continued focus on working capital management including strong collections performance.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $91 million, which was an increase over the minus $75 million we delivered in Q1.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $585 million in the quarter, an excellent result and up 26% as compared to prior year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Free cash flow, defined as operating cash flow less capex, for the quarter equaled $155 million compared to our expectation of about $200 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "Which quarter did Marathon Petroleum Corporation return the highest amount via share repurchases and dividends after 2022?", "answer": "Q1 2023", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 8, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "MPC returned over $3.5 billion via share repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "MPC returned nearly $3.4 billion via share repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "MPC returned nearly $3.1 billion via share repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "MPC returned $2.8 billion via share repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Highlighting our steadfast commitment to superior shareholder returns, MPC returned $2.5 billion via repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "MPC returned $2.9 billion through share repurchases and $290 million in dividends during the quarter. ", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "MPC returned $2.7 billion through share repurchases and $273 million in dividends during the quarter and in October, we repurchased $500 million of MPC shares", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "And MPC returned almost $1.3 billion through share repurchases, exclusive of excise tax payments, and $292 million in dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Skechers U.S.A., Inc.’s China sales growth, operating margin, effective tax rate, and earnings per share guidance in 2024-q2?", "answer": "3.4% on a constant-currency basis, 9.6%, 19.7%, and down slightly due to timing of demand creation spending.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "In China, sales grew 3.4% year over year on a constant-currency basis.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Earnings from operations were $206.5 million, a decrease of 5.1% compared to the prior year, and operating margin for the quarter was 9.6% compared to 10.8% last year primarily due to investments in brand building and global expansion.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our effective tax rate for the second quarter was 19.7% compared to 17.7% in the prior year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Earnings per share will be down slightly in the quarter due primarily to the timing of demand creation spending, which is typically highest during the second quarter as we amplify consumer awareness for our product portfolio and position our brand for a successful summer and back-to-school periods.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What were EOG Resources, Inc.'s free cash flow, share repurchase authorization increase, and dividend payment in 2024-Q3?", "answer": "$1.5 billion, $5 billion increase, and $0.91 per share.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EOG Resources, Inc.", "stock_code": "EOG", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We generated $1.6 billion of adjusted net income and $1.5 billion of free cash flow and returned $1.3 billion of that free cash flow back to our shareholders through a mix of our regular dividend and opportunistic share repurchases.", "ect_filename": "energy-EOG-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EOG Resources, Inc.", "stock_code": "EOG", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "In addition to announcing third quarter results yesterday, we demonstrated confidence in our ability to generate strong free cash flow in the future, as well as our continued commitment to return a significant portion of cash to our shareholders by increasing the regular dividend 7% and boosting our share repurchase authorization by $5 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-EOG-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EOG Resources, Inc.", "stock_code": "EOG", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Finally, we paid a $0.91 per share dividend and repurchased $758 million of shares during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-EOG-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter did Prudential Financial, Inc. achieve the highest individual retirement sales in the period from 2023-Q3 to 2024-Q2?", "answer": "2024-Q2", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Individual retirement posted $2 billion in sales, up 40% from the prior-year quarter.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Individual Retirement posted $2.1 billion in sales, reaching the highest level since the third quarter of 2019.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Individual Retirement posted $3.3 billion in sales, our best quarter in sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Individual retirement posted $3.5 billion in sales, its best quarter of sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Home Depot Inc’s comparable store sales, gross margin, and effective tax rate in 2024-Q4?", "answer": "Positive 0.8%, approximately 32.8%, and 22.9%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "During the fourth quarter, our total company comps were positive 0.8% with comps of negative 1.7% in November, positive 6.6% in December, and negative 2% in January.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "In the fourth quarter, our gross margin was approximately 32.8%, a decrease of 25 basis points from the fourth quarter last year, reflecting a change in mix as a result of the SRS acquisition, which was in line with our expectations.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "In the fourth quarter, our effective tax rate was 22.9% and for the year was approximately 23.7%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the lowest operating margin among Yum China, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., and Home Depot Inc in 2024-q1?", "answer": "Yum China had the lowest operating margin at 12.6%.", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.6%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Additionally, we achieved gross margins of 52.5% and an operating margin of 13.3%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the first quarter was 13.9%, compared to 14.9% in the first quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What was Baidu Inc.'s net income attributable to Baidu in each quarter from 2026 Q3 to 2027 Q2?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2023-q2 did Western Digital Corporation have the highest non-GAAP gross margin?", "answer": "Q4 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 6, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We reported third-quarter revenue of $2.8 billion, non-GAAP gross margin of 11%, and a non-GAAP loss per share of $1.37.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Gross margin for the fiscal fourth quarter was 3.9%, down 6.7 percentage points sequentially and 28.4 percentage points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Gross margin for the first quarter was 4.1%, which was at the higher end of the guidance range provided in July and included $225 million in underutilization expenses and 9 million in other one-time charges.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Gross margin was 15.5%, above the guidance range provided in October and improving 11.4 percentage points sequentially while declining 1.9 percentage points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Western Digital delivered excellent results in the quarter with revenue of $3.5 billion non-GAAP gross margin of 29.3% and non-GAAP earnings per share of $0.63, all of which exceeded expectations.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Western Digital delivered strong results with fiscal fourth-quarter revenue of $3.8 billion, non-GAAP gross margin of 36.3%, and non-GAAP earnings per share of $1.44.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "How many company-owned Skechers stores were opened in each quarter by Skechers U.S.A., Inc. during the period Q2 2026 to Q4 2026?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was Baidu Inc.'s net income attributable to the company in each quarter after 2023 Q3?", "answer": "RMB 2.6 billion in 2023 Q4, RMB 5.4 billion in 2024 Q1, RMB 5.5 billion in 2024 Q2, RMB 7.6 billion in 2024 Q3, and RMB 5.2 billion in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "In Q4, net income attributable to Baidu was RMB 2.6 billion, and diluted earnings per ADS was RMB 6.77.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Net income attributable to Baidu was RMB 5.4 billion, and diluted earnings per ADS were RMB 14.91.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Net income attributable to Baidu was RMB 5.5 billion and diluted earnings per ADS were RMB 15.01.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Net income attributable to Baidu was RMB 7.6 billion, and diluted earnings per ADS was RMB 21.6.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "In Q4, net income attributable to Baidu was RMB 5.2 billion, and diluted earnings per ADS was RMB 14.26.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Prudential Financial, Inc.'s cost savings target achievement, retail outflows impact, assets under management movement, individual retirement sales performance, and capital-efficient product sales performance in 2022?", "answer": "$750 million cost savings target achieved one year ahead of schedule, retail outflows primarily in fixed income due to the rising rate environment, positive institutional net flows more than offset by retail outflows, over $12 billion in sales for simplified solutions like FlexGuard and FlexGuard Income, and FlexGuard Life reached its highest sales quarter since its launch.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "This includes investing in products and solutions that meet the evolving needs of our customers and achieving our $750 million cost savings target one year ahead of schedule.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2022-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "PGIM experienced retail outflows, primarily in fixed income, consistent with industry trends, due to the rising rate environment, while institutional net flows continue to be positive.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2022-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "For 2022, PGIM experienced positive institutional net flows that were more than offset by retail outflows, primarily in fixed income, consistent with industry trends due to the rising rate environment.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2022-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "In individual retirement, product pivots have resulted in continued strong sales of more simplified solutions like FlexGuard and FlexGuard Income, representing over $12 billion of sales since inception, as well as increased fixed annuity sales.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2022-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "These increases include the benefit from the strength and breadth of our distribution capabilities and expansion of our product offerings, including our pivot toward more capital-efficient products like FlexGuard Life, which reached its highest sales quarter since its launch in 2022.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What was DBS Group Holdings Ltd.'s free cash flow in each quarter after 2023 Q4?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was GAC Group H's GAAP effective tax rate in each quarter after 2023 Q4?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were the operating margins of JD.com, Yum China, Crocs, Inc., and Home Depot Inc in Q3 2024?", "answer": "5%, 12.1%, 25.4%, and 13.5%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Moreover, our non-GAAP operating income increased by 18% year on year, and operating margin came in at 5% in Q3, up 54 bps year on year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our OP margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.1% and 100 basis points higher year over year or 140 basis points higher on a comparable basis.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our third-quarter adjusted operating margin was 25.4%, down 290 basis points from 28.3% in the prior year, driven by planned investments and SG&A.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the third quarter was 13.5%, compared to 14.3% in the third quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company opened the highest number of new stores among Home Depot Inc, Crocs, Inc., and Yum China in 2024-q2?", "answer": "Yum China", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "During the second quarter, we opened three new stores, bringing our total store count to 2,340.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "From a distribution perspective, we opened 13 new HEYDUDE outlet locations in the quarter, bringing our total year-to-date openings to 19.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We opened a record 779 net new stores in the first half and reached 15,423 total number of stores.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "Which quarter did Marathon Petroleum Corporation return the highest amount via share repurchases and dividends after 2023-q2?", "answer": "Q3 2023", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 6, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "MPC returned nearly $3.1 billion via share repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "MPC returned $2.8 billion via share repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Highlighting our steadfast commitment to superior shareholder returns, MPC returned $2.5 billion via repurchases and dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "MPC returned $2.9 billion through share repurchases and $290 million in dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "MPC returned $2.7 billion through share repurchases and $273 million in dividends during the quarter and in October, we repurchased $500 million of MPC shares.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "And MPC returned almost $1.3 billion through share repurchases, exclusive of excise tax payments, and $292 million in dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was DXC Technology Company's gross margin in each quarter after 2023 Q4?", "answer": "21.1% in 2024 Q1, 23.4% in 2024 Q2, and 22.4% in 2024 Q3, and 23.6% in Q4", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our first quarter gross margin of 21.1% was up 10 basis points year over year but below our expectation due to the revenue shortfall.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our second quarter gross margin of 23.4% was up 120 basis points year over year and 230 basis points sequentially, benefiting from our cost reduction initiatives.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our third quarter gross margin of 22.4% was up 70 basis points year over year, benefiting from our ongoing labor and nonlabor cost reductions.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Gross margin equaled 23.6%, flat year to year as we continued to drive workforce optimization and reduce our real estate footprint in the face of declining revenue.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was Realty Income Corporation's AFFO per share guidance range in each year after 2024?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2023 Q3 did Marathon Petroleum Corporation have the lowest operating costs per barrel?", "answer": "Q2 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Operating costs in the first quarter are expected to be $5.85 per barrel, higher sequentially due mainly to lower throughput volumes associated with the significant planned turnaround activity.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Operating costs are projected to be $4.95 per barrel in the second quarter, much lower than the first quarter, reflecting the benefit of running our system near full utilization and lower expected operating costs.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Operating costs are projected to be $5.35 per barrel in the third quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Operating costs are projected to be $5.50 per barrel.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "For the quarter, operating costs are projected to be $5.70 per the barrel.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2024-q4 did Autodesk Inc achieve the highest percentage increase in total deferred revenue?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2023-q4 did EPAM Systems Inc. have the lowest GAAP effective tax rate?", "answer": "Q1 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 6%, which included a higher level of excess tax benefits related to stock-based compensation.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 26.3%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24.3%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 28.1%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24.1%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 24.8%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "Which quarter did Prudential Financial, Inc. achieve the highest Individual Retirement sales during 2023-Q4 through 2024-Q3?", "answer": "Q3 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Individual Retirement posted $2.1 billion in sales, reaching the highest level since the third quarter of 2019.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Individual Retirement posted $3.3 billion in sales, our best quarter in sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Individual retirement posted $3.5 billion in sales, its best quarter of sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Individual retirement posted $3.6 billion in sales, its best quarter of sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the free cash flow of Western Digital Corporation, EPAM Systems Inc, Autodesk Inc, DXC Technology Company, and Baidu Inc in Q2 2026?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were the projected operating costs per barrel for Marathon Petroleum Corporation in each quarter of 2024?", "answer": "$5.70 per barrel in Q1, $4.95 per barrel in Q2, $5.35 per barrel in Q3, and $5.50 per barrel in Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "For the quarter, operating costs are projected to be $5.70 per the barrel. ", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Operating costs are projected to be $4.95 per barrel in the second quarter, much lower than the first quarter, reflecting the benefit of running our system near full utilization and lower expected operating costs.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Operating costs are projected to be $5.35 per barrel in the third quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Operating costs are projected to be $5.50 per barrel.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company opened the highest number of new stores in 2024-q2 among Crocs, Inc., Yum China, and Home Depot Inc?", "answer": "Yum China", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "From a distribution perspective, we opened 13 new HEYDUDE outlet locations in the quarter, bringing our total year-to-date openings to 19.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We opened a record 779 net new stores in the first half and reached 15,423 total number of stores.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "During the second quarter, we opened three new stores, bringing our total store count to 2,340.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter did Skechers U.S.A., Inc. achieve the highest year-over-year growth rate in direct-to-consumer sales during 2023-Q3 to 2024-Q1?", "answer": "2023-Q3", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Direct-to-consumer sales grew 24% year over year to 850.4 million, driven by increases of 33% internationally and 14% domestically.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "We continue to see strength in our direct-to-consumer segment, which increased 20% and for the first time exceeded 50% of our total sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Skechers excels where comfort and value intersect as evidenced by the strength of our global direct-to-consumer business, which grew 17% year over year to $829.9 million.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter between 2023 Q4 and 2024 Q2 did Western Digital Corporation incur the lowest operating loss?", "answer": "Q2 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Operating loss in the quarter was 478 million driven mainly by underutilization charges, inventory write-downs, and other items totaling 272 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Operating loss was 443 million, which included underutilization charges and inventory write-downs totaling 234 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Operating loss in the quarter was 91 million, which included underutilization charges of 156 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Home Depot Inc.’s sales performance, total sales, comparable store sales growth, operating margin, effective tax rate, and return on invested capital in Q4 2023?", "answer": "Sales were largely in line with expectations, $34.8 billion, negative 3.5%, approximately 11.9%, 24%, and approximately 31.3%, respectively.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 6, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "As you heard from Ted, during the fourth quarter, our sales were largely in line with our expectations.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "In the fourth quarter, total sales were $34.8 billion, a decrease of 2.9% from last year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "During the fourth quarter, our total company comps were negative 3.5% with comps of negative 2.5% in November, positive 1.1% in December, and negative 8.5% in January.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the fourth quarter was approximately 11.9% and, for the year, was approximately 14.2%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "In the fourth quarter and for fiscal 2023, our effective tax rate was 24%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Computed on the average of beginning and ending long-term debt and equity for the trailing 12 months, return on invested capital was approximately 31.3%, down from 36.7% in the fourth quarter of fiscal 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What year had the lowest expected sustaining capital expenditures for enterprise products partners l.p. after 2020?", "answer": "2022", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Enterprise Products Partners L.P.", "stock_code": "EPD", "sector": "energy", "year": "2020", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "We currently expect sustaining capital expenditures for 2021 to be approximately $440 million, which includes $115 million of expenditures associated with scheduled turnarounds of our PDH propane dehydrogenation facility and our octane enhancement facility.", "ect_filename": "energy-EPD-2020-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Enterprise Products Partners L.P.", "stock_code": "EPD", "sector": "energy", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "For 2022, we currently expect growth capital investments to be approximately $1.5 billion and sustaining capital expenditures to be approximately $350 million.", "ect_filename": "energy-EPD-2022-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Enterprise Products Partners L.P.", "stock_code": "EPD", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We continue to expect sustaining capital expenditures for 2023 will be approximately $400 million.", "ect_filename": "energy-EPD-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Enterprise Products Partners L.P.", "stock_code": "EPD", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "2024 sustaining capital expenditures are elevated due to planned turnarounds for our PDH 1 plant and our iBDH facility and our high-purity isobutylene facility.", "ect_filename": "energy-EPD-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Enterprise Products Partners L.P.", "stock_code": "EPD", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "We expect 2025 sustaining capital expenditures will be approximately $525 million, which includes a planned turnaround on our octane enhancement plan.", "ect_filename": "energy-EPD-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter did Autodesk Inc. experience the highest increase in billings from 2023-Q1 to 2024-Q3?", "answer": "Q4 2023", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 7, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Billings increased 16% to $1.1 billion, reflecting robust underlying demand.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Billings increased 17% to $1.2 billion, reflecting robust underlying demand.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Billings increased 16% to $1.4 billion, reflecting continued solid underlying demand, partly offset by foreign exchange movements and a shift in mix from multiyear upfront to annual contracts versus expectations.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Billings increased 28% to $2.1 billion, our first quarter over $2 billion, reflecting continued solid underlying demand and a tailwind from both our largest multiyear renewal cohort and the pending removal of the discount for multiyear contracts billed upfront.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Billings increased 4% to $1.2 billion, primarily reflecting growing renewal rates and early renewals, partly offset by about one month of annual billings for most multiyear contracts.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We had a full quarter impact in the second quarter, which resulted in billings declining 8%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We had the second full quarter impact in our third fiscal quarter, which resulted in billings declining 11%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company reported the highest adjusted EBITDA among Marathon Petroleum Corporation, ONEOK, Inc., and Enterprise Products Partners L.P. in 2023-q2?", "answer": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Adjusted EBITDA was $4.5 billion for the quarter and cash flow from operations excluding favorable working capital changes was over $3.1 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Second-quarter adjusted EBITDA totaled $971 million, a 10% increase year over year.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Enterprise Products Partners L.P.", "stock_code": "EPD", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We reported adjusted EBITDA of 2.4 billion, compared to 2.2 billion in the same quarter of last year.", "ect_filename": "energy-EPD-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the occupancy rate for The Macerich Company, Simon Property Group, Inc., and Realty Income Corporation in 2024 q3?", "answer": "The occupancy rates for The Macerich Company, Simon Property Group, Inc., and Realty Income Corporation in 2024-Q3 were as follows: The Macerich Company's occupancy improved over the previous quarter (specific percentage not provided), Simon Property Group, Inc.'s malls and outlet occupancy was 96.2%, and Realty Income Corporation's occupancy was 98.7%, which represents a 10 basis point decrease from the prior quarter.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "The Macerich Company", "stock_code": "MAC", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our occupancy, leasing activity, and same-store NOI improved over the previous quarter.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-MAC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Simon Property Group, Inc.", "stock_code": "SPG", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Malls and outlet occupancy at the end of the third quarter was 96.2%, an increase of 1% compared to the prior year.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-SPG-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Realty Income Corporation", "stock_code": "O", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We finished the quarter with 98.7% occupancy, a 10 basis point decrease from the prior quarter.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-O-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "How many new locations did Crocs, Inc., Home Depot Inc, and Yum China open in 2026-q2?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were Home Depot Inc.’s new store openings, total sales growth, and organic growth in 2025?", "answer": "13 new stores, approximately 2.8%, and mid-single-digit organic growth.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "For fiscal 2025, we plan to open 13 new stores.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "For fiscal 2025, we expect total sales growth of approximately 2.8%, comparable sales growth of approximately 1%, and adjusted diluted earnings per share to decline approximately 2%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "And for the year, we expect SRS to deliver mid-single-digit organic growth.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the free cash flow of Autodesk Inc, Baidu Inc, DXC Technology Company, Western Digital Corporation, and EPAM Systems Inc in Q2 2023?", "answer": "$627 million, RMB 7.9 billion, $17 million, an outflow of $240 million, and $52 million.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Today, we reported record second quarter revenue, non-GAAP operating margin, and free cash flow.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was RMB 7.9 billion.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow of $17 million, leaving us a little better than breakeven free cash flow for the first 6 months of the year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "operating cash flow for the second quarter was $35 million, and free cash flow was an outflow of $240 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $52 million, compared to free cash flow of $82 million in the same quarter last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "During which quarter did EPAM Systems Inc. have the lowest GAAP effective tax rate between 2023 Q3 and 2024 Q2?", "answer": "2024 Q1", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 26.3%, which includes a one-time tax charge connected to the disposal of holdings in Russia and lower-than-expected excess tax benefits related to stock-based compensation.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 23.4% versus our Q4 guide of 24%, due to greater-than-expected excess tax benefits related to stock-based compensation, partially offset by higher state taxes and the impact of losses in certain non-US acquired subsidiaries.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 6%, which included a higher level of excess tax benefits related to stock-based compensation.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 26.3%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24.3%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter did Marathon Petroleum Corporation report the lowest refining operating costs between 2023 and 2024?", "answer": "Q2 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $5.15 per barrel in the second quarter, lower sequentially and due to higher throughput and lower energy costs.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $5.14 per barrel in the third quarter, flat sequentially.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $5.67 per barrel in the fourth quarter, higher sequentially due to higher energy costs, particularly on the West Coast, as well as higher project-related expenses associated with planned turnaround activity.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $6.14 per barrel in the first quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $4.97 per barrel in the second quarter, lower, sequentially, primarily due to higher throughputs, lower project-related expenses associated with reduced turnaround activity, and lower energy costs.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Home Depot Inc.'s adjusted diluted earnings per share, diluted earnings per share, and capital expenditures in 2024-Q4?", "answer": "$3.13, $3.02, and $1.1 billion.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Adjusted diluted earnings per share were $3.13, compared to $2.86 in the prior year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our diluted earnings per share for the fourth quarter were $3.02, an increase of approximately 7% compared to the fourth quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "During the fourth quarter, we invested approximately $1.1 billion back into our business in the form of capital expenditures.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were EOG Resources, Inc.'s share repurchase program status, adjusted earnings per share, free cash flow, and production guidance achievement in 2026-Q2?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were Skechers U.S.A., Inc.'s projected sales for each fiscal year before 2026?", "answer": "$5.8 billion to $5.9 billion in 2021, $7.2 billion to $7.4 billion in 2022, $7.95 billion to $8.05 billion in 2023, $8.925 billion to $8.975 billion in 2024, and $9.7 billion to $9.8 billion in 2025.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2021", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "For fiscal year 2021, we expect sales to be in the range of between $5.8 billion and $5.9 billion and net earnings per diluted share to be in the range of between $1.80 and $2.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2021-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "For fiscal 2022, we expect sales to be in the range of $7.2 billion to $7.4 billion and net earnings per diluted share to be in the range of $2.60 to $2.70.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2022-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "For the full year, we expect sales in the range of 7.95 billion to 8.05 billion and net earnings per share in the range of $3.33 to $3.43.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "For the full year 2024, we expect sales in the range of $8.925 billion to $8.975 billion, and earnings per diluted share in the range of $4.20 to $4.25, representing annual growth of 12% and 21%, respectively, at the midpoint.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "For the full year 2025, we expect sales in the range of $9.7 billion to $9.8 billion.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Marathon Petroleum Corporation’s adjusted earnings per share, capital expenditures, and the issuance amount of senior unsecured notes in 2024-q2?", "answer": "$4.12, $541 million, and $1.65 billion.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "MPC generated second-quarter adjusted earnings per share of $4.12.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "This quarter, capital expenditures and investments were $541 million.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "And during the second quarter, MPLX issued $1.65 billion in tenured senior notes, the proceeds of which MPLX expects to use to retire senior notes maturing in December of this year and February of next year.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Prudential's Individual Retirement sales in each quarter after 2023 Q3?", "answer": "$2.1 billion in 2023 Q4, $3.3 billion in 2024 Q1, $3.5 billion in 2024 Q2, $3.6 billion in 2024 Q3, and $3.6 billion in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Individual Retirement posted $2.1 billion in sales, reaching the highest level since the third quarter of 2019.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Individual Retirement posted $3.3 billion in sales, our best quarter in sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Individual retirement posted $3.5 billion in sales, its best quarter of sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Individual retirement posted $3.6 billion in sales, its best quarter of sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Individual retirement posted $3.6 billion in sales in the fourth quarter, its best quarter of sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were jd.com's net revenue growth, product revenue growth, general merchandise revenue growth, net income, and free cash flow in 2026-Q3?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2023-Q4 did Nissan Motor Co., Ltd. have the lowest operating costs per barrel?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was Western Digital Corporation's gross margin in each quarter after 2023 Q2?", "answer": "10.6% in 2023 Q3, 3.9% in 2023 Q4, 4.1% in 2024 Q1, 15.5% in 2024 Q2, 29.3% in 2024 Q3, and 36.3% in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 6, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Gross margin for the fiscal third quarter was 10.6%, down 6.8 percentage points sequentially and 21.1 percentage points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Gross margin for the fiscal fourth quarter was 3.9%, down 6.7 percentage points sequentially and 28.4 percentage points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Gross margin for the first quarter was 4.1%, which was at the higher end of the guidance range provided in July and included $225 million in underutilization expenses and 9 million in other one-time charges.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Gross margin was 15.5%, above the guidance range provided in October and improving 11.4 percentage points sequentially while declining 1.9 percentage points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Gross margin was 29.3%, well above the guidance range.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "In the fiscal fourth quarter, total gross margin reached 36.3%, well above the guidance range.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2024-Q2 did Marathon Petroleum Corporation return the highest amount via share repurchases and dividends?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What has been the largest annual growth capital expenditures estimate for Enterprise Products Partners L.P. after 2021?", "answer": "2024, with an estimate in the range of $3.5 billion to $3.75 billion.", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Enterprise Products Partners L.P.", "stock_code": "EPD", "sector": "energy", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We continue to expect our total 2022 growth capital expenditures to be approximately $1.6 billion and sustaining capex to be approximately $350 million.", "ect_filename": "energy-EPD-2022-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Enterprise Products Partners L.P.", "stock_code": "EPD", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We continue to expect our growth capital expenditures for 2023 will be in the range of $2.4 billion to $2.8 billion, depending on any incremental system expansions and timing.", "ect_filename": "energy-EPD-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Enterprise Products Partners L.P.", "stock_code": "EPD", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our current estimate of growth capital expenditures for 2024 is now in the range of 3.5 billion to 3.75 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-EPD-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter did Prudential achieve the highest sales in Individual Retirement from Q4 2023 to Q3 2024?", "answer": "Q3 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Individual Retirement posted $2.1 billion in sales, reaching the highest level since the third quarter of 2019.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Individual Retirement posted $3.3 billion in sales, our best quarter in sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Individual retirement posted $3.5 billion in sales, its best quarter of sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Individual retirement posted $3.6 billion in sales, its best quarter of sales in over a decade.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter did Skechers U.S.A., Inc. experience the largest year-over-year percentage growth in direct-to-consumer sales during the period from 2022 Q3 to 2024 Q2?", "answer": "Q2 2023", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 8, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Sales increased 12% in the quarter due to growth of 14% in the Americas, 10% in APAC and 6% in EMEA.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2022-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Domestic direct-to-consumer sales increased 30% due to strong triple-digit growth in our e-commerce channel, as well as a double-digit increase in our brick-and-mortar stores.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2022-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Direct-to-consumer sales increased 24% year over year to $707.4 million, driven by 25% growth domestically and 24% growth internationally.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Direct-to-consumer sales grew 29% year over year to $939.5 million, representing nearly 47% of total sales for the quarter.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Direct-to-consumer sales grew 24% year over year to 850.4 million, driven by increases of 33% internationally and 14% domestically.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "We continue to see strength in our direct-to-consumer segment, which increased 20% and for the first time exceeded 50% of our total sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Skechers excels where comfort and value intersect as evidenced by the strength of our global direct-to-consumer business, which grew 17% year over year to $829.9 million.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Direct-to-consumer increased 9.2%, resulting in sales of more than $1 billion for the quarter, a first for the company.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "Since the start of 2023, during which quarter did EPAM Systems Inc.’s EMEA region post its highest year‑over‑year revenue growth in constant currency?", "answer": "Q1 2023", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 8, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "EMEA, representing 38% of our Q1 revenues, grew 10% year over year, or 13.3% in constant currency.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "EMEA, representing 39% of our Q2 revenues, grew 8.5% year over year or 6.5% in constant currency.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "EMEA, representing 39% of our Q3 revenues, grew 1.8% year over year and decreased 3.5% in constant currency.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "EMEA, representing 39% of our Q4 revenues, was flat year over year and declined 3.5% in constant currency.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "EMEA representing 39% of our Q1 revenues contracted 3.2% year over year and 4.8% in constant currency.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "EMEA representing 38% of our Q2 revenues, contracted 6% year over year and 5.6% in constant currency.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "EMEA, representing 38% of our Q3 revenues, contracted 0.3% year over year and 1.3% in constant currency.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "EMEA, representing 38% of our Q4 revenues, increased 3.1% year over year, reflecting negative 1.4% organic and positive 4.5% inorganic growth.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the free cash flow of Western Digital Corporation, Autodesk Inc, DXC Technology Company, EPAM Systems Inc, and Baidu Inc in Q1 2026?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "In which quarter did Western Digital Corporation achieve the highest non-GAAP earnings per share between Q4 2026 and Q4 2026?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were the operating margins of JD.com, Yum China, Crocs, Inc., and Home Depot Inc in 2024-q3?", "answer": "5%, 12.1%, 25.4%, and 13.5%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Moreover, our non-GAAP operating income increased by 18% year on year, and operating margin came in at 5% in Q3, up 54 bps year on year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our OP margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.1% and 100 basis points higher year over year or 140 basis points higher on a comparable basis.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our third-quarter adjusted operating margin was 25.4%, down 290 basis points from 28.3% in the prior year, driven by planned investments and SG&A.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the third quarter was 13.5%, compared to 14.3% in the third quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What were the operating margins for JD.com, Crocs, Inc., Yum China, and Home Depot Inc in 2024-q3?", "answer": "5%, 25.4%, 12.1%, and 13.5%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Moreover, our non-GAAP operating income increased by 18% year on year, and operating margin came in at 5% in Q3, up 54 bps year on year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our third-quarter adjusted operating margin was 25.4%, down 290 basis points from 28.3% in the prior year, driven by planned investments and SG&A.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our OP margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.1% and 100 basis points higher year over year or 140 basis points higher on a comparable basis.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the third quarter was 13.5%, compared to 14.3% in the third quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter did Cincinnati Financial Corporation experience the highest growth rate in bond interest income over the period 2023-Q3 to 2024-Q1?", "answer": "2024-Q1", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Bond interest income continued to show strong growth, up 19% for the third quarter of this year.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Bond interest income, again, grew at a good pace, up 19% for the fourth quarter of the year.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Bond interest income grew 21% for the first quarter of this year.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What was EPAM Systems Inc.'s utilization rate in each quarter after 2023 Q4?", "answer": "76.8% in 2024 Q1, 77.5% in 2024 Q2, 76.4% in 2024 Q3, and 76.2% in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Utilization was 76.8%, compared to 74.9% in Q1 of last year, and 74.4% in Q4 2023.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Utilization was 77.5%, compared to 75.1% in Q2 of last year and 76.8% in Q1 2024.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Utilization was 76.4% compared to 72.7% in Q3 of last year and 77.5% in Q2 2024.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Utilization was 76.2%, compared to 74.4% in Q4 of last year and 76.4% in Q3 2024.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Western Digital Corporation's projected revenue targets in each quarter after 2024-q1?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|nonfact", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were Prudential's pre-tax adjusted operating income, assets under management growth, and earnings per share guidance in 2024-q3?", "answer": "$1.6 billion, 15%, and $3.48 per share.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our pre-tax adjusted operating income was $1.6 billion or $3.48 per share on an after-tax basis for the third quarter of 2024 and $9.98 on a year-to-date basis, which is up 6%.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "PGIM's assets under management increased by 15% and to $1.4 trillion from the year ago quarter, driven by market appreciation, investment performance and net flows.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "These adjustments combined get us to a baseline of $3.48 per share for the third quarter.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Skechers U.S.A., Inc.'s expected full-year sales in each year before 2025?", "answer": "$5.8 billion to $5.9 billion in 2021, $7.2 billion to $7.4 billion in 2022, $7.95 billion to $8.05 billion in 2023, and $8.925 billion to $8.975 billion in 2024.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2021", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "For fiscal year 2021, we expect sales to be in the range of between $5.8 billion and $5.9 billion and net earnings per diluted share to be in the range of between $1.80 and $2.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2021-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "For fiscal 2022, we expect sales to be in the range of $7.2 billion to $7.4 billion and net earnings per diluted share to be in the range of $2.60 to $2.70.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2022-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "For the full year, we expect sales in the range of 7.95 billion to 8.05 billion and net earnings per share in the range of $3.33 to $3.43.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "For the full year 2024, we expect sales in the range of $8.925 billion to $8.975 billion, and earnings per diluted share in the range of $4.20 to $4.25, representing annual growth of 12% and 21%, respectively, at the midpoint.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "In which year did EPAM Systems Inc. have the highest expected amortization of intangibles?", "answer": "2022", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2020", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Amortization of intangibles is expected to be approximately $12.5 million for the year, evenly spread across each quarter.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2020-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2021", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Amortization of intangibles is expected to be approximately $24 million for the year, evenly spread across each quarter.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2021-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Amortization of intangibles is expected to be approximately 22 million for the year evenly spread across each quarter.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2022-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Amortization of intangibles is expected to be approximately $26 million for the year, evenly spread across each quarter", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Amortization of intangibles is expected to be approximately 68 million for the year, with approximately 18 million in Q1 and 17 million in each remaining quarter.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the operating margin of Lowe's Companies, Inc., CNH Industrial N.V., Helmerich & Payne, Inc., FactSet Research Systems Inc., and Commercial Metals Company in 2024-q1?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was VICI Properties Inc.'s AFFO per share growth in each quarter of 2023-Q3, 2023-Q4, and 2024-Q1?", "answer": "10.7%, 8.8%, and 6.1%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "VICI Properties Inc.", "stock_code": "VICI", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Finally, in a year in which REIT earnings growth has generally been difficult to come by, VICI's AFFO per share earnings in Q3 grew 10.7% year over year.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-VICI-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "VICI Properties Inc.", "stock_code": "VICI", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Just touching on the income statement, AFFO per share was $0.55 for the quarter, an increase of 8.8% compared to $0.51 for the quarter ended December 31, 2022.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-VICI-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "VICI Properties Inc.", "stock_code": "VICI", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "The effects of the transactions and relationships announced at the end of last year and the beginning of this year contributed to our 6.1% growth in AFFO per share.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-VICI-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What were the operating margins of JD.com, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., Home Depot Inc, Crocs, Inc., and Yum China in 2026-q1?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was Crocs, Inc.'s adjusted diluted earnings per share in each year after 2020?", "answer": "$8.32 in 2021, $10.92 in 2022, $12.03 in 2023, and $13.17 in 2024.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2021", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Full-year adjusted diluted earnings per share also more than doubled to $8.32.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2021-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Full year adjusted diluted earnings per share increased 31% to $10.92.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2022-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "For the full year, our adjusted diluted earnings per share increased 10% to $12.03.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Adjusted diluted earnings per share increased 9% to $13.17.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was Skechers U.S.A., Inc.'s total cash, cash equivalents, and investments at the end of each quarter after 2024 Q4?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were Prudential Financial, Inc.'s sales performance, benefits ratio change, and cost savings target achievement in 2022?", "answer": "FlexGuard Life reached its highest sales quarter since its launch, the group insurance benefits ratio improved from lower COVID mortality, and the $750 million cost savings target was achieved one year ahead of schedule.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "These increases include the benefit from the strength and breadth of our distribution capabilities and expansion of our product offerings, including our pivot toward more capital-efficient products like FlexGuard Life, which reached its highest sales quarter since its launch in 2022.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "And our group insurance benefits ratio has improved during the year from lower COVID mortality.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2022-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "This includes investing in products and solutions that meet the evolving needs of our customers and achieving our $750 million cost savings target one year ahead of schedule.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2022-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What were the operating margins of Home Depot Inc, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., and Crocs, Inc. in Q1 2026?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "In which quarter did The Macerich Company experience the highest same-center NOI growth during the period from Q2 2025 to Q1 2026?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "Which company had the highest free cash flow among Western Digital Corporation, DXC Technology Company, Baidu Inc, and EPAM Systems Inc in 2026-q2?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "Which company had the highest operating margin in 2024-q1 among Skechers U.S.A., Inc., Home Depot Inc, JD.com, and Crocs, Inc.?", "answer": "Crocs, Inc. with an adjusted operating margin of 27.1%.", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Additionally, we achieved gross margins of 52.5% and an operating margin of 13.3%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the first quarter was 13.9%, compared to 14.9% in the first quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "JD Retail non-GAAP operating profit decreased by 5%, and operating margin was down 50 bps year on year to 4.1% in Q1, in line with our [Inaudible] moving on to JD Logistics, revenues of JD Logistics increased by 15% year on year in Q1, with strong momentum for both of its internal and external revenues.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our first quarter adjusted operating margin declined 80 basis points to 27.1% compared to 27.9% for the same period last year, but was favorable to our expectations on higher gross margins and favorable revenue, leveraging our cost base.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter did Home Depot Inc. return the highest amount to shareholders in the form of share repurchases during the period from Q2 2025 to Q4 2026?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was the free cash flow for Western Digital Corporation, EPAM Systems Inc, Baidu Inc, and Autodesk Inc in 2023-q2?", "answer": "An outflow of $240 million, $52 million, RMB 7.9 billion, $246 million.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "operating cash flow for the second quarter was $35 million, and free cash flow was an outflow of $240 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $52 million, compared to free cash flow of $82 million in the same quarter last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was RMB 7.9 billion.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We delivered record second quarter free cash flow of $246 million, up 32% year over year, reflecting strong billings growth in both Q1 and Q2.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Marathon Petroleum Corporation's refining operating costs per barrel in each quarter after 2023 Q1?", "answer": "$5.15 in 2023 Q2, $5.14 in 2023 Q3, $5.67 in 2023 Q4, $6.14 in 2024 Q1, $4.97 in 2024 Q2, $5.30 in 2024 Q3, and $5.26 in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 7, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $5.15 per barrel in the second quarter, lower sequentially and due to higher throughput and lower energy costs.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $5.14 per barrel in the third quarter, flat sequentially.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $5.67 per barrel in the fourth quarter, higher sequentially due to higher energy costs, particularly on the West Coast, as well as higher project-related expenses associated with planned turnaround activity.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $6.14 per barrel in the first quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $4.97 per barrel in the second quarter, lower, sequentially, primarily due to higher throughputs, lower project-related expenses associated with reduced turnaround activity, and lower energy costs.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $5.30 per barrel in the third quarter, higher sequentially primarily due to lower throughputs and higher project-related expenses associated with increased turnaround activity.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our refineries ran at 94% utilization, processing nearly 2.8 million barrels of crude per day, and refining operating costs were $5.26 per barrel in the fourth quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Skechers U.S.A., Inc.'s accounts receivable amounts at the end of each quarter after Q4 2024?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were Marathon Petroleum Corporation's operating costs per barrel in each quarter after 2024 Q4?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was EPAM Systems Inc.'s non-GAAP income from operations as a percentage of revenue in each quarter after 2023 Q2?", "answer": "17% in 2023 Q3, 17.3% in 2023 Q4, 14.9% in 2024 Q1, 15.2% in 2024 Q2, 19.1% in 2024 Q3 and 16.7% 2024 Q4", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 6, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Non-GAAP income from operations was $196 million or 17% of revenue in the quarter compared to $232 million or 18.9% of revenue in Q3 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Non-GAAP income from operations was $200 million or 17.3% of revenue in the quarter, compared to $220 million or 17.8% of revenue in Q4 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Non-GAAP income from operations was $174 million or 14.9% of revenue in the quarter, compared to $178 million or 14.7% of revenue in Q1 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Non-GAAP income from operations was $175 million or 15.2% of revenue in the quarter, compared to $191 million or 16.3% of revenue in Q2 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Non-GAAP income from operations was 223 million or 19.1% of revenue in the quarter compared to 196 million or 17% of revenue in Q3 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Non-GAAP income from operations was 208 million or 16.7% of revenue in the quarter, compared to 200 million or 17.3% of revenue in Q4 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the highest operating margin among Skechers U.S.A., Inc., Home Depot Inc, and JD.com in Q2 2025?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "Which quarter had the largest billings increase for Autodesk Inc during the specified period?", "answer": "2023-Q4", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Billings increased 16% to $1.4 billion, reflecting continued solid underlying demand, partly offset by foreign exchange movements and a shift in mix from multiyear upfront to annual contracts versus expectations.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Billings increased 28% to $2.1 billion, our first quarter over $2 billion, reflecting continued solid underlying demand and a tailwind from both our largest multiyear renewal cohort and the pending removal of the discount for multiyear contracts billed upfront.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Billings increased 4% to $1.2 billion, primarily reflecting growing renewal rates and early renewals, partly offset by about one month of annual billings for most multiyear contracts.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We had a full quarter impact in the second quarter, which resulted in billings declining 8%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We had the second full quarter impact in our third fiscal quarter, which resulted in billings declining 11%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter did jd.com experience the highest year-on-year growth rate in net revenue during the period from 2023 to 2024 Q1?", "answer": "Q2 2023", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our net revenue grew by 1.4% year-on-year to RMB 243 billion in Q1 as we continued to focus on user quality and building deeper user engagement, we are encouraged to see that.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our net revenues grew by 8% year on year to RMB 288 billion in Q2.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our net revenues grow by 2% year on year to RMB 248 billion in Q3.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our net revenues grew by 4% year on year to RMB 306 billion in Q4 and RMB 1.1 trillion for full year 2023, as we navigated a mix of macro recovery, seasonality factors, and our strategic refocus.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our net revenues grow by 7% year on year to RMB 260 billion in Q1.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the highest operating margin among Koh Young Technology, Stifel Financial Corp., Arista Networks, Inc., and Cameco Corporation in 2024-q1?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was the operating margin of Skechers U.S.A., Inc., Home Depot Inc, Crocs, Inc., and Yum China in 2024-q1?", "answer": "13.3%, 13.9%, 27.1%, and 12.6%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Additionally, we achieved gross margins of 52.5% and an operating margin of 13.3%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the first quarter was 13.9%, compared to 14.9% in the first quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our first quarter adjusted operating margin declined 80 basis points to 27.1% compared to 27.9% for the same period last year, but was favorable to our expectations on higher gross margins and favorable revenue, leveraging our cost base.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.6%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company reported the largest growth in bond interest income among Simon Property Group, Inc., EOG Resources, Inc., Autodesk Inc, Iron Mountain Incorporated, Home Depot Inc, Realty Income Corporation, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., and Markel Group Inc. in 2024-q1?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|nonfact", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "In which quarter did Cincinnati Financial Corporation achieve the best property casualty combined ratio during 2026?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What was EPAM Systems Inc.'s GAAP effective tax rate in each quarter after 2023 Q4?", "answer": "6% in 2024 Q1, 26.3% in 2024 Q2, 28.1% in 2024 Q3, and 24.8% in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 6%, which included a higher level of excess tax benefits related to stock-based compensation.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 26.3%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24.3%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 28.1%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24.1%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 24.8%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the free cash flow for Baidu Inc, Western Digital Corporation, Autodesk Inc, DXC Technology Company, and EPAM Systems Inc in 2023-q2?", "answer": "RMB 7.9 billion, an outflow of $240 million, record free cash flow, $17 million, and $52 million.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was RMB 7.9 billion.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "operating cash flow for the second quarter was $35 million, and free cash flow was an outflow of $240 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Today, we reported record second quarter revenue, non-GAAP operating margin, and free cash flow.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow of $17 million, leaving us a little better than breakeven free cash flow for the first 6 months of the year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $52 million, compared to free cash flow of $82 million in the same quarter last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were the effective tax rates of Home Depot Inc, Yum China, and Skechers U.S.A., Inc. in 2024-q2?", "answer": "24.5%, 25.2%, and 19.7%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "In the second quarter, our effective tax rate was 24.5%, compared to 24.4% in the second quarter of fiscal 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our effective tax rate was 25.2% in the second quarter, on par with the same period last year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our effective tax rate for the second quarter was 19.7% compared to 17.7% in the prior year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Simon Property Group, Inc.'s dividend increase, mall and outlet occupancy rate, leasing activity, total leases signed, occupancy costs, senior unsecured notes issuance, and liquidity in 2024-Q3?", "answer": "$2.10, 96.2%, 1,200 leases for 4 million square feet, more than 3,900 leases for 15 million square feet which is expected to generate more than $1 billion of revenue, 12.8%, $1 billion in senior notes with a 4.75% interest rate, and $11.1 billion.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 7, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Simon Property Group, Inc.", "stock_code": "SPG", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We raised our dividend again to $2.10.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-SPG-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Simon Property Group, Inc.", "stock_code": "SPG", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Malls and outlet occupancy at the end of the third quarter was 96.2%, an increase of 1% compared to the prior year.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-SPG-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Simon Property Group, Inc.", "stock_code": "SPG", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We signed approximately 1,200 leases for 4 million square feet in the quarter.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-SPG-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Simon Property Group, Inc.", "stock_code": "SPG", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Through the first nine months of 2024, we have signed more than 3,900 leases for 15 million square feet which is expected to generate more than $1 billion of revenue.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-SPG-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Simon Property Group, Inc.", "stock_code": "SPG", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "At the end of the quarter, our occupancy cost was 12.8%.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-SPG-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Simon Property Group, Inc.", "stock_code": "SPG", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We also issued $1 billion in senior notes with a term of 10 years and a 4.75% interest rate.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-SPG-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Simon Property Group, Inc.", "stock_code": "SPG", "sector": "real_estate", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We ended the quarter with approximately $11.1 billion of liquidity.", "ect_filename": "real_estate-SPG-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2023-Q4 did Baidu Inc. have the highest net income?", "answer": "Q3 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Net income attributable to Baidu was RMB 5.4 billion, and diluted earnings per ADS were RMB 14.91.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Net income attributable to Baidu was RMB 5.5 billion and diluted earnings per ADS were RMB 15.01.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Net income attributable to Baidu was RMB 7.6 billion, and diluted earnings per ADS was RMB 21.6.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "In Q4, net income attributable to Baidu was RMB 5.2 billion, and diluted earnings per ADS was RMB 14.26.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the lowest operating margin in 2024-q2 among Skechers U.S.A., Inc., JD.com, Home Depot Inc, and Yum China?", "answer": "JD.com", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Earnings from operations were $206.5 million, a decrease of 5.1% compared to the prior year, and operating margin for the quarter was 9.6% compared to 10.8% last year primarily due to investments in brand building and global expansion.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "JD Retail's operating profit increased by 24% year on year to RMB 10 billion with operating margin recording a 72-bps expansion to 3.9%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the second quarter was 15.1%, compared to 15.4% in the second quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Restaurant margins stabilized, OP margin expanded to 9.9%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "During which quarter did Bio-Rad Laboratories, Inc. experience the highest occupancy rate between 2023-q2 and 2024-q1?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were EPAM Systems Inc.’s Americas revenue growth, non-GAAP diluted EPS, cash and cash equivalents, utilization rate, effective tax rates, stock-based compensation expense forecast, and amortization of intangibles in 2024 Q4?", "answer": "11.4% total with 2.7% organic and 8.7% inorganic, $2.84, approximately $1.3 billion, 76.2%, approximately 26% GAAP and 24% non-GAAP, approximately $44 million, and approximately $9 million.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 7, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "From a geographic perspective, the Americas, our largest region, representing 60% of our Q4 revenues, increased 11.4% year over year, reflecting 2.7% organic and 8.7% inorganic growth.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our non-GAAP diluted EPS was $2.84, reflecting an increase of $0.09 or 3.3% compared to the same quarter in 2023.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "We ended the quarter with approximately 1.3 billion in cash and cash equivalents, which is lower compared to the same quarter last year due to our recently completed acquisitions.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Utilization was 76.2%, compared to 74.4% in Q4 of last year and 76.4% in Q3 2024.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "We expect our GAAP effective tax rate to be approximately 26% and our non-GAAP effective tax rate to be approximately 24%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Stock-based compensation expense is expected to be approximately 44 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Amortization of intangibles is expected to be approximately 9 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company reported the highest adjusted EBITDA among Enterprise Products Partners L.P., ONEOK, Inc., and Marathon Petroleum Corporation in 2023-q2?", "answer": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Enterprise Products Partners L.P.", "stock_code": "EPD", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We reported adjusted EBITDA of 2.4 billion, compared to 2.2 billion in the same quarter of last year.", "ect_filename": "energy-EPD-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Second-quarter adjusted EBITDA totaled $971 million, a 10% increase year over year.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Adjusted EBITDA was $4.5 billion for the quarter and cash flow from operations excluding favorable working capital changes was over $3.1 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "During 2023 Q4 to 2024 Q2, in which quarter did Munich Re achieve the highest operating margin?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "In which quarter did ONEOK, Inc. achieve the highest net income between Q3 2022 and Q1 2024?", "answer": "Q1 2023", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 7, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "ONEOK's third quarter 2022 net income totaled $432 million or $0.96 per share, a 10% increase compared with the third quarter of 2021 and a 4% increase when compared with the second quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2022-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "ONEOK's fourth quarter and full year 2022 net income totaled $485 million and $1.72 billion, respectively, representing increases of 28% for the fourth quarter and 15% for the full year compared with the same period in 2021.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2022-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "ONEOK's first quarter 2023 net income totaled 1.05 billion, or $2.34 per share, and adjusted EBITDA for the period totaled $1.72 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "ONEOK's second-quarter 2023 net income totaled $468 million or $1.04 per share.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "ONEOK's third quarter 2023 net income totaled $454 million or $0.99 per share.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "ONEOK's fourth quarter and full year 2023 net income totaled $688 million and $2.7 billion, respectively.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "ONEOK's first quarter 2024 net income totaled $639 million or $1.09 per share, and adjusted EBITDA for the period totaled $1.44 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "During which quarter from late 2023 to mid-2024 did Skechers U.S.A., Inc. achieve the largest year-over-year percentage growth in its direct-to-consumer segment?", "answer": "Q4 2023", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "We continue to see strength in our direct-to-consumer segment, which increased 20% and for the first time exceeded 50% of our total sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Skechers excels where comfort and value intersect as evidenced by the strength of our global direct-to-consumer business, which grew 17% year over year to $829.9 million.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Direct-to-consumer increased 9.2%, resulting in sales of more than $1 billion for the quarter, a first for the company.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What was EPAM Systems, Inc.'s GAAP income from operations in each quarter after 2024 Q1?", "answer": "$121 million in 2024 Q2, 177 million in 2024 Q3, and $137 million in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "GAAP income from operations was $121 million or 10.5% of revenue in the quarter, compared to $144 million or 12.3% of revenue in Q2 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "GAAP income from operations was 177 million or 15.2% of revenue in the quarter compared to 114 million or 9.9% of revenue in Q3 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "GAAP income from operations was 137 million or 10.9% of revenue in the quarter, compared to 122 million or 10.6% of revenue in Q4 of last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "Which quarter had the lowest refining operating costs for Marathon Petroleum Corporation after 2024-q1?", "answer": "Q2 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $4.97 per barrel in the second quarter, lower, sequentially, primarily due to higher throughputs, lower project-related expenses associated with reduced turnaround activity, and lower energy costs.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $5.30 per barrel in the third quarter, higher sequentially primarily due to lower throughputs and higher project-related expenses associated with increased turnaround activity.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our refineries ran at 94% utilization, processing nearly 2.8 million barrels of crude per day, and refining operating costs were $5.26 per barrel in the fourth quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the adjusted EBITDA of ONEOK, Inc., Marathon Petroleum Corporation, and Enterprise Products Partners L.P. in 2023-q2?", "answer": "$971 million, $4.5 billion, and $2.4 billion.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Second-quarter adjusted EBITDA totaled $971 million, a 10% increase year over year.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Adjusted EBITDA was $4.5 billion for the quarter and cash flow from operations excluding favorable working capital changes was over $3.1 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Enterprise Products Partners L.P.", "stock_code": "EPD", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We reported adjusted EBITDA of 2.4 billion, compared to 2.2 billion in the same quarter of last year.", "ect_filename": "energy-EPD-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company reported the highest free cash flow among Autodesk Inc, EPAM Systems Inc, Western Digital Corporation, and Baidu Inc in 2023-q1?", "answer": "Baidu Inc", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "As Andrew mentioned, we delivered record first-quarter free cash flow of $422 million, up 34% year over year, reflecting strong billings growth in both Q4 and Q1.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $123 million, compared to free cash flow of $79 million in the same quarter last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Operating cash flow for the first quarter was $6 million and free cash flow was an outflow of $215 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Free cash flow was RMB 4.5 billion.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2023-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What was Home Depot Inc.'s gross margin in each quarter after Q4 2024?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "In which quarter did ONEOK, Inc. achieve the highest earnings per share (EPS) from Q3 2022 to Q2 2024?", "answer": "Q1 2023", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 8, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "ONEOK's third quarter 2022 net income totaled $432 million or $0.96 per share, a 10% increase compared with the third quarter of 2021 and a 4% increase when compared with the second quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2022-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2022", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "ONEOK's fourth quarter and full year 2022 net income totaled $485 million and $1.72 billion, respectively, representing increases of 28% for the fourth quarter and 15% for the full year compared with the same period in 2021.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2022-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "ONEOK's first quarter 2023 net income totaled 1.05 billion, or $2.34 per share, and adjusted EBITDA for the period totaled $1.72 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "ONEOK's second-quarter 2023 net income totaled $468 million or $1.04 per share.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "ONEOK's third quarter 2023 net income totaled $454 million or $0.99 per share.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "ONEOK's fourth quarter and full year 2023 net income totaled $688 million and $2.7 billion, respectively.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "ONEOK's first quarter 2024 net income totaled $639 million or $1.09 per share, and adjusted EBITDA for the period totaled $1.44 billion.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "ONEOK, Inc.", "stock_code": "OKE", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "ONEOK's second-quarter 2024 net income totaled $780 million or $1.33 per share, representing an earnings per share increase of 28% compared with the second quarter of 2023 and a 22% compared with the prior quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-OKE-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Skechers U.S.A., Inc.'s accounts receivable at quarter-end in each quarter from Q4 2023 to Q3 2024?", "answer": "$860.3 million, $1.16 billion, $1.03 billion, and $1.19 billion.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter end were $860.3 million, essentially flat compared to the prior year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter-end were $1.16 billion, an increase of $105.7 million compared to the prior year reflecting higher wholesale sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter-end were $1.03 billion, an increase of $87 million compared to the prior year, reflecting higher wholesale sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter-end were $1.19 billion, an increase of $257.7 million compared to the prior year, reflecting higher wholesale sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What were aon plc's total revenue growth, adjusted operating margin, organic revenue growth, and operating margin expansion in 2024-q3?", "answer": "26%, 24.6%, 7%, and 70 basis points.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Aon plc", "stock_code": "AON", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "With this organic growth and the addition of NFP, we delivered 26% total revenue growth, 28% adjusted operating income growth, and adjusted operating margin of 24.6%, an increase of 70 basis points year over year from our combined 2023 margin baseline.", "ect_filename": "financials-AON-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Aon plc", "stock_code": "AON", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "With this organic growth and the addition of NFP, we delivered 26% total revenue growth, 28% adjusted operating income growth, and adjusted operating margin of 24.6%, an increase of 70 basis points year over year from our combined 2023 margin baseline.", "ect_filename": "financials-AON-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Aon plc", "stock_code": "AON", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Second, our organic revenue growth reached 7% in the third quarter.", "ect_filename": "financials-AON-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Aon plc", "stock_code": "AON", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "And when doing so, operating margin expanded 70 basis points in the quarter.", "ect_filename": "financials-AON-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "Which quarter after 2023-q3 saw the highest non-GAAP gross margin for Western Digital Corporation?", "answer": "Q4 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Gross margin for the fiscal fourth quarter was 3.9%, down 6.7 percentage points sequentially and 28.4 percentage points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Gross margin for the first quarter was 4.1%, which was at the higher end of the guidance range provided in July and included $225 million in underutilization expenses and 9 million in other one-time charges.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Gross margin was 15.5%, above the guidance range provided in October and improving 11.4 percentage points sequentially while declining 1.9 percentage points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Western Digital delivered excellent results in the quarter with revenue of $3.5 billion non-GAAP gross margin of 29.3% and non-GAAP earnings per share of $0.63, all of which exceeded expectations.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Western Digital delivered strong results with fiscal fourth-quarter revenue of $3.8 billion, non-GAAP gross margin of 36.3%, and non-GAAP earnings per share of $1.44.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Skechers U.S.A., Inc.'s accounts receivable at the end of each quarter from Q3 2023 to Q2 2024?", "answer": "$929.4 million, $860.3 million, $1.16 billion, and $1.03 billion.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter end were 929.4 million, essentially flat compared to the prior year and in line with our wholesale business.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter end were $860.3 million, essentially flat compared to the prior year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter-end were $1.16 billion, an increase of $105.7 million compared to the prior year reflecting higher wholesale sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter-end were $1.03 billion, an increase of $87 million compared to the prior year, reflecting higher wholesale sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the non-GAAP operating income, dividend income decline, and investment income growth of Cincinnati Financial Corporation. in 2024-q3?", "answer": "$224 million, 1%, and 15%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Non-GAAP operating income of $224 million for the third quarter was down $37 million from a year ago, driven by an $86 million increase in after-tax catastrophe losses.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Dividend income was down 1%, reflecting $959 million of net sales of equity securities during the third quarter, primarily from some portfolio rebalancing through trimming or exiting positions of seven common stocks among our 63 holdings at the beginning of the quarter.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Cincinnati Financial Corporation", "stock_code": "CINF", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Investment income had another round of strong growth, up 15% for the third quarter of '24, compared with the same quarter in '23.", "ect_filename": "financials-CINF-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What was Getlink Group's GAAP effective tax rate in each quarter after 2023 Q2?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were Baidu Inc's total revenue, operating expenses, net income, free cash flow, and cash flow contribution from its mobile ecosystem in 2024-Q1?", "answer": "RMB 31.5 billion, RMB 10.7 billion, RMB 5.4 billion, RMB 4.2 billion, healthy margins and strong.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Mobile ecosystem has continued to deliver healthy margins and strong free cash flow.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Total revenues were RMB 31.5 billion, increasing 1% year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Operating expenses were RMB 10.7 billion, decreasing 2% year over year, primarily due to a decrease in personnel-related expenses and other R&D expenditures, partially offset by the increase in server depreciation expenses and server custody fees, which support GenAI research and development inputs.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Net income attributable to Baidu was RMB 5.4 billion, and diluted earnings per ADS were RMB 14.91.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Free cash flow was RMB 4.2 billion.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the free cash flow for DXC Technology Company, Western Digital Corporation, Baidu Inc, Autodesk Inc, and EPAM Systems Inc in 2023-q2?", "answer": "$17 million, an outflow of $240 million, RMB 7.9 billion, $246 million, and $52 million.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow of $17 million, leaving us a little better than breakeven free cash flow for the first 6 months of the year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "operating cash flow for the second quarter was $35 million, and free cash flow was an outflow of $240 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was RMB 7.9 billion.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "We delivered record second quarter free cash flow of $246 million, up 32% year over year, reflecting strong billings growth in both Q1 and Q2.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $52 million, compared to free cash flow of $82 million in the same quarter last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2023-Q3 did Skechers U.S.A., Inc. report the highest year-over-year increase in accounts receivable?", "answer": "Q3 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter end were $860.3 million, essentially flat compared to the prior year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter-end were $1.16 billion, an increase of $105.7 million compared to the prior year reflecting higher wholesale sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter-end were $1.03 billion, an increase of $87 million compared to the prior year, reflecting higher wholesale sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter-end were $1.19 billion, an increase of $257.7 million compared to the prior year, reflecting higher wholesale sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Accounts receivable at quarter end were $990.6 million, an increase of $130.3 million compared to the prior year, reflecting higher wholesale sales.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was DXC Technology Company's free cash flow in each quarter after 2023 Q4?", "answer": "Negative $75 million in 2024 Q1, $91 million in 2024 Q2, $585 million in 2024 Q3, and $155 million in 2024 Q4.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Free cash flow for the quarter was negative $75 million, ahead of our expectations due to continued focus on working capital management including strong collections performance.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $91 million, which was an increase over the minus $75 million we delivered in Q1.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $585 million in the quarter, an excellent result and up 26% as compared to prior year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "DXC Technology Company", "stock_code": "DXC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Free cash flow, defined as operating cash flow less capex, for the quarter equaled $155 million compared to our expectation of about $200 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-DXC-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company among Home Depot Inc, JD.com, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., and Yum China had the highest operating margin in 2024-q2?", "answer": "Home Depot Inc", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the second quarter was 15.1%, compared to 15.4% in the second quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "As JD Logistics continued to benefit from its increased scale and improved operating efficiency, its non-GAAP operating margin also increased by 370 bps year on year in the quarter, hitting a new record of 4.9% since its listing.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Earnings from operations were $206.5 million, a decrease of 5.1% compared to the prior year, and operating margin for the quarter was 9.6% compared to 10.8% last year primarily due to investments in brand building and global expansion.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Restaurant margins stabilized, OP margin expanded to 9.9%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter after 2023 did Western Digital Corporation achieve the highest gross margin?", "answer": "Q4 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "relative-time query", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Gross margin for the first quarter was 4.1%, which was at the higher end of the guidance range provided in July and included $225 million in underutilization expenses and 9 million in other one-time charges.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Gross margin was 15.5%, above the guidance range provided in October and improving 11.4 percentage points sequentially while declining 1.9 percentage points year over year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Gross margin was 29.3%, well above the guidance range.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "In the fiscal fourth quarter, total gross margin reached 36.3%, well above the guidance range.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Iron Mountain Incorporated’s EBITDA, adjusted EBITDA, constant currency revenue growth, adjusted EBITDA margin, and AFFO growth in 2026-Q1?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "What were Marathon Petroleum Corporation’s adjusted EBITDA, cash flow from operations, and operating cash flow in 2024-Q4?", "answer": "$2.1 billion, $1.7 billion, and $1.7 billion.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Adjusted EBITDA was approximately $2.1 billion for the quarter, and $11.3 billion for the year.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Cash flow from operations, excluding working capital changes, was $1.7 billion for the quarter and nearly $8.2 billion for the year.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Operating cash flow, excluding changes in working capital, was $1.7 billion in the quarter, driven by both our refining and midstream businesses.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the highest free cash flow among Western Digital Corporation, Baidu Inc, Autodesk Inc, and EPAM Systems Inc in 2023-q1?", "answer": "Baidu Inc", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Western Digital Corporation", "stock_code": "WDC", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Operating cash flow for the first quarter was $6 million and free cash flow was an outflow of $215 million.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-WDC-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Baidu Inc", "stock_code": "BIDU US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Free cash flow was RMB 4.5 billion.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-BIDU_US-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Autodesk Inc", "stock_code": "ADSK US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Today, we reported record first-quarter revenue, non-GAAP operating margin, and free cash flow fueled by strong demand and a robust, competitive performance.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-ADSK_US-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Free cash flow was $123 million, compared to free cash flow of $79 million in the same quarter last year.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter did EPAM Systems Inc. report the lowest GAAP effective tax rate from 2023 to mid-2024?", "answer": "Q1 2024", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "We expect our GAAP effective tax rate to be approximately 20% and our non-GAAP effective tax rate, which excludes excess tax benefits related stock-based compensation, to be approximately 23%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 26.3%, which includes a one-time tax charge connected to the disposal of holdings in Russia and lower-than-expected excess tax benefits related to stock-based compensation.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 23.4% versus our Q4 guide of 24%, due to greater-than-expected excess tax benefits related to stock-based compensation, partially offset by higher state taxes and the impact of losses in certain non-US acquired subsidiaries.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2023-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 6%, which included a higher level of excess tax benefits related to stock-based compensation.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "EPAM Systems Inc", "stock_code": "EPAM US", "sector": "information_technology", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Our GAAP effective tax rate for the quarter came in at 26.3%, and our non-GAAP effective tax rate was 24.3%.", "ect_filename": "information_technology-EPAM_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Prudential’s pre-tax adjusted operating income, operating income per share, and cash and liquid assets in 2024-Q3?", "answer": "$1.6 billion, $3.48 on an after-tax basis, and $4.3 billion.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our pre-tax adjusted operating income was $1.6 billion or $3.48 per share on an after-tax basis for the third quarter of 2024 and $9.98 on a year-to-date basis, which is up 6%.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our pre-tax adjusted operating income was $1.6 billion or $3.48 per share on an after-tax basis for the third quarter of 2024 and $9.98 on a year-to-date basis, which is up 6%.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q3.json"}, {"company_name": "Prudential Financial, Inc.", "stock_code": "PRU", "sector": "financials", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q3", "evidence": "Our cash and liquid assets were $4.3 billion, which is above our minimum liquidity target of $3 billion, and we have substantial off-balance sheet resources.", "ect_filename": "financials-PRU-2024-q3.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Home Depot Inc's new store openings, share repurchases, and sales growth in 2023-Q2?", "answer": "2 new stores, approximately $2 billion, and 0.6%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "During the second quarter, we opened two new stores bringing our total store count to 2,326.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2023", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "And during the quarter, we paid approximately $2.1 billion in dividends to our shareholders, and we returned approximately $2 billion to shareholders in the form of share repurchases.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2023-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Sales for the second quarter were $43.2 billion, an increase of 0.6% from the same period last year.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "Which company had the highest gross margin among JD.com, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., and Home Depot Inc in 2024-q4?", "answer": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "On our consolidated profit performance at the group level, gross margin increased to 15.3% in Q4 and 15.9% for the full year of 2024, up 110 bps and 114 bps, respectively.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "Gross margin was 53.3%, up 20 basis points compared to the prior year, primarily due to a favorable channel mix.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "In the fourth quarter, our gross margin was approximately 32.8%, a decrease of 25 basis points from the fourth quarter last year, reflecting a change in mix as a result of the SRS acquisition, which was in line with our expectations.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was ONEOK, Inc.'s net income in each quarter from Q4 of 2026 to Q3 of 2027?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
{"question": "Which company had the highest operating margin in 2024-q1 among Skechers U.S.A., Inc., Yum China, Home Depot Inc, Crocs, Inc., and JD.com?", "answer": "Crocs, Inc.", "reasoning_type": "comparison", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Additionally, we achieved gross margins of 52.5% and an operating margin of 13.3%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.6%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the first quarter was 13.9%, compared to 14.9% in the first quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our first quarter adjusted operating margin declined 80 basis points to 27.1% compared to 27.9% for the same period last year, but was favorable to our expectations on higher gross margins and favorable revenue, leveraging our cost base.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "JD Retail non-GAAP operating profit decreased by 5%, and operating margin was down 50 bps year on year to 4.1% in Q1, in line with our [Inaudible] moving on to JD Logistics, revenues of JD Logistics increased by 15% year on year in Q1, with strong momentum for both of its internal and external revenues.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Marathon Petroleum Corporation’s shareholder returns, refining operating costs, senior unsecured notes issuance, and share repurchases in 2024-Q2?", "answer": "$3.19 billion, $4.97 per barrel, $1.65 billion, and $2.9 billion.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 4, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "During his tenure, Mike delivered its transformative strategic priorities and returned a peer-leading $40 billion to shareholders.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "Refining operating costs were $4.97 per barrel in the second quarter, lower, sequentially, primarily due to higher throughputs, lower project-related expenses associated with reduced turnaround activity, and lower energy costs.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "And during the second quarter, MPLX issued $1.65 billion in tenured senior notes, the proceeds of which MPLX expects to use to retire senior notes maturing in December of this year and February of next year.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}, {"company_name": "Marathon Petroleum Corporation", "stock_code": "MPC", "sector": "energy", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q2", "evidence": "MPC returned $2.9 billion through share repurchases and $290 million in dividends during the quarter.", "ect_filename": "energy-MPC-2024-q2.json"}]}
{"question": "What were Home Depot Inc's new store openings, total sales growth, and organic growth in 2025?", "answer": "13 new stores, 2.8% total sales growth, and mid-single-digit organic growth.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-keywords", "num_hops": 3, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "For fiscal 2025, we plan to open 13 new stores.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "For fiscal 2025, we expect total sales growth of approximately 2.8%, comparable sales growth of approximately 1%, and adjusted diluted earnings per share to decline approximately 2%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q4", "evidence": "And for the year, we expect SRS to deliver mid-single-digit organic growth.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q4.json"}]}
{"question": "What was the operating margin for JD.com, Skechers U.S.A., Inc., Yum China, Home Depot Inc, and Crocs, Inc. in 2024-q1?", "answer": "4.1%, 13.3%, 12.6%, 13.9%, and 27.1%.", "reasoning_type": "enumeration", "question_type": "single-time query|multi-companies", "num_hops": 5, "evidence_list": [{"company_name": "JD.com", "stock_code": "JD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "JD Retail non-GAAP operating profit decreased by 5%, and operating margin was down 50 bps year on year to 4.1% in Q1, in line with our [Inaudible] moving on to JD Logistics, revenues of JD Logistics increased by 15% year on year in Q1, with strong momentum for both of its internal and external revenues.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-JD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Skechers U.S.A., Inc.", "stock_code": "SKX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Additionally, we achieved gross margins of 52.5% and an operating margin of 13.3%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-SKX-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Yum China", "stock_code": "YUMC US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin as a percentage of revenue was 12.6%.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-YUMC_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Home Depot Inc", "stock_code": "HD US", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our operating margin for the first quarter was 13.9%, compared to 14.9% in the first quarter of 2023.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-HD_US-2024-q1.json"}, {"company_name": "Crocs, Inc.", "stock_code": "CROX", "sector": "consumer_discretionary", "year": "2024", "quarter": "q1", "evidence": "Our first quarter adjusted operating margin declined 80 basis points to 27.1% compared to 27.9% for the same period last year, but was favorable to our expectations on higher gross margins and favorable revenue, leveraging our cost base.", "ect_filename": "consumer_discretionary-CROX-2024-q1.json"}]}
{"question": "In which quarter did Prudential have the highest amount of cash and liquid assets between 2026-Q4 and 2027-Q2?", "answer": "unanswerable", "reasoning_type": "unanswerable|out-of-scope", "question_type": "multi-time query", "num_hops": 0, "evidence_list": []}
